From the day we arrive
കല(ഒഗക്ഗ്‌ ഗ്ഒ 4൧൭
On the planet
൧0 ൧൧൩ ൨
And, blinking, step into the sun
൧0൭൧, ൧ല്കഥാഒെ, നല'ഒറ്റഷ്ഗ ൭൧൭൦ ൭ ടട നദഗെഗ്‌
There's more to see
൧ഒഥുക്ലറഷ്ഗററ ൧ലസ്ധ വ്ഥലനദ്‌
Than can ever be seen
28ലഥ൦ഗഠ്ഥറ ഒഠ൭ ൭൧ ൧ഠ൭൨ ൨൧0൧൦൩൭൧
More to do
ഥ്ഥുക്ലറഷ്ഗററ ഥലസ്ധ വ്‌൭ഡക്ഥ
Than can ever be done
8ലഥഗഠ്ഥറ ൧൭ ൭൧ ൧2ഠ൭൨ വഒഡ്രഥ
There's far too much
7ഖല്ഒഥ ഥാ
To take in here
ഗ്രഗഥ ഗദ ന്‌ ഥ്‌
More to find
ഒഥുക്ലഷ്ഗററ ഥലസ്ധ വ്ഠ്ഥ്‌
Than can ever be found
28ലഥ൭൦ഗഠ്ഥറ ഒഠ൭ ൭൧ ൧ഠ൭൨ ൨൦9൧
But the sun rolling high
7ഒ൧ ന ഒഒഗക്ഗ്‌ ഗലഡ്ഥ്‌ ഗ്‌
Through the sapphire sky
൧ 'ററ്റ്‌ നല ഥ്‌
Keeps great and small
റെറുലഷഷക്ഗൃഷഗറ്റ ൧2ടെദ7 നദഗഥാഥ (ഥ്‌
On the endless round
൧൭'ഒ ാഥ്ഒ7ഒഥ )൭ഥറ ൭൧൭൨
It's the circle of life
൧൧൭൧ 0൧5 ഥറുണറ (കഗറ്ഥാറ
And it moves us all
൧൭൧ 49 ഗന റ്റുലടഗകഗ ഗ്ഒ ലട
Through despair and hope
7ല൭൧ 7൭5൭ ഗ്ഗ ൭.൭ റ്൭റ ഗഖ്യാഥ
Through faith and love
7ല൭ഥ (ക്വാലഡദൃഷ൭ റ്റ (൭൭൧ കയേഷററ്റ
Till we find our place
൧0൭7 :ഗ്൭ നലലനഥ്‌ “ലന്വാദ! ഗ്ഒ
On the path unwinding
൧൭൧ഥ )൭൧ഥറ ൧൦൧ 777൨
In the circle
൧ ൭ഒന 0ാഥ5ഗറ്റണറ
The circle of life
൧5൧൭ :കറ്ഥാറെ
It's the circle of life
൧൧൭൧ 0൧5 ഥറുണറ (കഗറ്ഥാറ
And it moves us all
൭൧൮ സനെറ്റുലടശകഗ ഗ്ഒ ലട
Through despair and hope
7ല൭൧ 7൭5൭ ഗ്ഗ ൭.൭ റ്൭റ ഗഖ്യാഥ
Through faith and love
7ല൭ഥ (ക്വാലഡദൃഷ൭ റ്റ (൭൭൧ കയേഷററ്റ
Till we find our place
൧0൭7 :ഗ്൭ നലലനഥ്‌ “ലന്വാദ! ഗ്ഒ
On the path unwinding
൧൭൧ഥ )൭൧ഥറ ൧൦൧ 777൨
In the circle
൧ ൭ഒന 0ാഥ5ഗറ്റണറ
The circle of life
൧5൧൭ :കറ്ഥാറെ
Life's not fair, is it?
ലിഠ്ധ്വാ ബി മഠ, കന
You see, I... Well, I shall never be king.
ലോല, ടര... ട്ര 10 നബ്ദഠി ദ്യ.
And you shall never see the light of another day.
൧ഡഘില്ാധിദ മ്യ്ഥ നല്‍ ലന !ഒ!.
Didn't your mother ever tell you not to play with your food?
[ഗിധ്യിവല്ലാലന്മ നടം ഘം ലന്നമ്ന ലന നമിത ഖ്ല്റ്‌
What do you want?
യാന യല്ല
I'm here to announce that King Mufasa's on his way,
മുര ിഭ ട്‌ ധസ്ധിനനേധ്ധ്്ത്ന ലന ദല്യദ്്ഥ്ദടദ ടന ലാലി,
so you'd better have a good excuse for missing this morning's ceremony.
199 ലമി ടപടഠില്ത്ഥ മിദട ന്ഥ ഡേ്വലിന്മണ്ന നല്യവിട 0 9൦.
Oh, look, Zazu.
൭൨, ൩൦൭൦10൭൨0, ൧൭മ്വ.
You've made me lose my lunch.
മുര ഠ്ട്വശ്വിടാദന നല്൭൩൨൩.
You'll lose more than that when the king gets through with you.
൧ ലിത്ഥിഭ്വിദ്ബിലാന ി്വാദാദ വ ടടിലാദട ഠിഡിവണ ന്മ.
He's as mad as a hippo with a hernia.
൧9 മനില ന്ധിര.
I quiver with fear!
മയ നഘ്യാട്ഒ്ല ൬൫ ഭ്ലിഡ്ബ്‌
Now, Scar, don't look at me that way.
ലേ, ഠി ൧൩0 ഖരാലവ്ധ.
Help!
101൦!
Scar?
ടല?
Drop him.
[ല്ാമടിത്ഥ ഠി.
Impeccable timing, Your Majesty.
ലെറ്റ് നട നാ ടര, വ്വ.
Why, if it isn't my big brother descending from on high
൭൨, സ്വാ ലാന ടര ന ടാ നനന ധി
to mingle with the commoners.
ധന്ധിറാലമ്ധി ബോ ൦൭ ഷ്വാബഭിത്ല.
Sarabi and I didn't see you at the presentation of Simba.
മയ ൭൭ ലലാ! പന്പ ഠി ധ്യാ നലമ്വാലിഭന്മിത്ഥ ട്വ.
That was today?
പ്രാധാ ൧ ബിത്ന?
I feel simply awful!
മുര ടട ലാല ലാലട്ല്വ
Must've slipped my mind.
പചന്വാലിസുയ ട്ര 1 ല്ഥ്വാമ.
Yes, well, as slippery as your mind is,
വല്ല യ്ദധില യിലല ട്ര,
as the king's brother, you should've been first in line!
ടലാമറുദ! ദഠ(ന9 ഭ്വാദഠ്9 യ, ദ്ധ ഡേിറില ൦൭൫ ട്മനട ഠി ടല!
Well, I was first in line, until the little hairball was born.
മുയ്്ലറ നോ ന്മ നട്ലിടി ചിന്ന, വന്ാല്ല്വാധ്ച്സ ॥ല്വ്നത്ഥ.
That hairball is my son and your future king.
ദ്ധാലി്ധ്ഡ മലി നായി നലം! ഭ്വം ലിം
I shall practice my curtsy!
മുര മിത ഥാലിദ്ിറ ണനസ്ന്പാല്നഘന്നല്‍്‌
Don't turn your back on me, Scar.
പാ നന്ധാലല്ഖ്യിത് ടര, ട്വ.
Oh, no, Mufasa.
൭൨,ഠ്ച്പ്ഴീധ്ഒടമ.
Perhaps you shouldn't turn your back on me.
ഗ്ധ്ിന്൩ യല്ല ലാവ നലമ്പാല്ല്യ്ഘാത്ഥ ടര.
Is that a challenge?
ഠ്യ ടബ ലോ?
Temper, temper.
8:0൩, ലാല.
I wouldn't dream of challenging you.
മുര 1ലിറമബാാന ധന്ധിഗണനലാല യം.
Pity. Why not?
മൃയനാ ടര. ഇജ്വാദാധിദ ലന
Well, as far as brains go, I got the lion's share.
ഗി ടാ! ശ്വലദംനമ0, ടരില്സതനാ ലബത ഭിലാ1൫൩.
But when it comes to brute strength,
ലവി ഠിലി ടല്റ! ഭ്വമ്മീമിയി,
I'm afraid I'm at the shallow end of the gene pool.
നിസ ടര 1ദിവാല്ഘ്വാലാലിഷാഠില്‍മ.
There's one in every family, sire.
ഉദിദണ ടബില്വാഭ്ധു മട 39 5൦൦, സമ്ബിവ.
Two in mine, actually,
ഗില്‍, ഠ്ധട ഠ്ടിദണ ദ്ധ ടര,
and they always manage to ruin special occasions.
൦ നലഘല്‍ര ടസ്ിടടഃ നലാടമിറ്ഥ ഥി.
What am I going to do with him?
യാന ്ഡ്‌ ടപരാധമ്‌ റോസ്സ്‌?
He'd make a very handsome throw rug.
൧900൦1൦1 ഠ്വദഠിത്ഥ ഗലന്നല്ഠ്ബ വന മേബിം
Zazu!
ക്മമ്ധ!
And just think, whenever he gets dirty,
£॥നനത്വ0,വയിദ്ധ ഠദ ൪0,
you could take him out and beat him.
ന്വാഠില്വ്യന്ധ ഠിദ ഠി വധ ൦ നഹാദ്ധിസുയ.
Simba.
ന്നാ.
Dad! Dad!
ചുവ ചഷൃത്ല്‍്‌
Come on, dad, we gotta go! Wake up!
ല്രോഖില, ഷുത്വ, നലിട്ായ!! ദംഘഎ്ഥബ്ദ്ല്‍
Sorry.
ഗി.
Dad! Dad!
ചുവ ചഷൃത്ല്‍്‌
Your son is awake.
൧൩10 മഴമിറ്ല്വാലഥ്ന.
Before sunrise, he's your son.
ടലോല്ധന നമ്‌ പല ിദ നമി
Dad! Come on, Dad.
ചുവ ചില്‍, ൭൨.
You promised.
ഷുഖ് ല്വൃദല്വി.
Okay, Okay. I'm up, I'm up.
ര്യ, റിയു. ൧൭൨ ല്വോനാഥന, ദ്ല്വാഥ്ന.
Look, Simba.
1൦ ടാ.
Everything the light touches is our kingdom.
ലട ലാ! ട്നല നദ്ല്ഘി ദന ന൭.
Wow.
ഠാ.
A king's time as ruler rises and falls like the sun.
ലനല്സ്മ്മ ട്വ 1ല01 ഠി നല്ലി നമ്മ.
One day, Simba, the sun will set on my time here
ട്ധ ഘി സി, ടമ്പാ, നല്ല ഷ്യ ലിത്നാലലന്പ
and will rise with you as the new king.
ഠ്ാല്ധിട്ല്ാണനലസ്ല്മല യ ടലാമദ! ദൃ വരന 0ബ.
-And this'll all be mine? -Everything.
-ല്ധട ബി ലി്ത്ബ്യദഠി ബ്॥ഗടമര? ല്ലി.
Everything the light touches.
ലട ലാ! ട്നല ന്മ.
What about that shadowy place?
ദമധടണനാ ലാദയത്നാ ാധിാഠാല്ന്മന്മ?
That's beyond our borders.
൮ ഠിധല ടല്വാദഠ് 1൯൭.
You must never go there, Simba.
പ്‌ ടര 0൦9] ൫ ടന, ടസ്വാമ.
But I thought a king can do whatever he wants.
വല്യ ടമ ൭ ടം യം 0ഠില്വാധമ ടടടധിര ൫.
Oh, there's more to being king than getting your way all the time.
[ഴിലബുദഠി। ടന യവ ിലാ1൨ഠ്ദ്വാദഠ്ഃ ടലല്‍യ നഘാ॥ഡിഭല്ചന്ലി.
-There's more? -Simba...
-൧ഠ൭ 1൭17 -ടമ്പാമ...
Everything you see exists together in a delicate balance.
ല്ധട നടിന്ധി്വാഥോ ഴ്വ ്ല്ടണന ദടലമ്പാണബാണതന ദ്ധ 019.
As king, you need to understand that balance
ലാമ ദ്യ, ൩19 ാലിധ നനമ0൩ി ഭടലന്ധാനാന നഭലാധ്‌
and respect all the creatures,
൦ നഹാനാന്നമ്‌ ടന്ധട നലിന്്ധിം
from the crawling ant to the leaping antelope.
0ലിടന്ധഥ്ന ൭൦ നദിഡ്വാധന മന്ലിംദ൭ല ൩൭൨.
But, Dad, don't we eat the antelope?
ലവ, കമ, ബാന്മ നലിത്ഥ ണ്ടി?
Yes, Simba, but let me explain.
വ, മ്പ, ദ്രല കൃര്്വുടടടിതന.
When we die, our bodies become the grass,
്യാദ്ധിട 1൭ ന, ധാന ലാന്ധിയ നലം! ഡബന്പാധ്‌,
and the antelope eat the grass.
ടി ണ്ടി ാധിട നദ്ത്ഥ ബന്ധാഥ്‌.
And so we are all connected in the great circle of life.
പഠി 19 ടന്ധട ലി്ധാധനാ യ ിട്ണലാധടന ന ിഭ്വ്ോന.
-Good morning, sire! -Good morning, Zazu.
ലന ്!, ഡമ്ബിഡ്‌ ലന ്റ!, 23മ്വ.
Checking in with the morning report.
ദ്ധി ന്ധി ധന്ധിനല്പാലിത്ഥിട്ംന 1.
Fire away.
ലട.
Well! The buzz from the bees
ഗ്ന്വാല 0൩ നഹുദ്ലിത്ഥ
is that the leopards are in a bit of a spot.
ലയെ ലട ഥനട്ധ ലിത്വ ടി ാലന്നടടമില.
Really?
വല്യ?
What are you doing, son?
യാന യഥ്ധല്ഡ, നല്റ
Pouncing.
ഴിലലി൭ണ.
Let an old pro show you how it's done.
ദല മദന ബ്‌ ഡബ്വിനക്ന ലേബുര.
I told the elephants to forget it, but they can't...
ലച്തിനബ്ന്മ ല്യമ്നാല്മധ നലധഥ്വാമിയര്സമ, ട്വ ൮0൦1൦൨...
-Zazu, would you turn around? -Yes, sire.
-മമ്ധ, ൧001ല്‍ യ്ലിലാധട്നാത്നാദഠ്ടന? 821 ഡ്ധ്ബ്വ.
The cheetahs are hard up, but...
റലനട്ധ സ്ന നടടി ടോ...
Stay low to the ground.
മല്യാബിത്ഥ ധാധന യല്ല ൭൫൭൨.
Cheetahs never prosper...
റലനട്ധാസ്മനാ പറമ്ബുദഠ। ൧൩൭൧൭...
Yeah, okay. Stay low to the ground, right? Yeah.
മം ത്യ. മല്യാബിത്ഥ ധാധ്സിഭ നല ന.
-What going on? -A pouncing lesson.
്യാമ ല്‌? 10 നലലിതണ.
Very good. Pouncing.
ദമറ്റടിമ൨ഴിലിരണ.
Pouncing? No, sire, you can't be serious...
ഴിലലിരണന? പ്0൩, ബിവ, യ ാലാധ്ത്ധിയ...
This is so humiliating.
ബി നബി നന്ദിത.
Try not to make a sound.
പ്ാബാധമടലാലനാ ധി.
What are you telling him, Mufasa?
യാന യയാ ഡ,വര്‍്ഥ്ദടദ്‌?
Mufasa? Simba?
ഗ്ഥ്ടടാ? ടമ്പാട?
That's very good.
ദറ്റ്ട ടര.
-Zazu! -Yes!
-കമമ്ധി!
-News from the underground. -Now, this time...
ഒല ഠിക്ലി ഗമ ൩൭. ടല്ഷ്വനാ, യ ബ്‌...
Sire! Hyenas in the Pride Lands!
ദധബിഡയ്‌ ഥധാധിറവലല നലലഘാംവ 100 ഥഥഠ്ല!
Zazu, take Simba home.
മമ്ധ, റാ മ്പാ ധി.
Dad, can't l come?
ഷരപല്ലധം്വ്ത ടിയ
No, son.
1ിധാഠിലല്‍, ന.
I never get to go anywhere.
മയ ിനാടഥനാലധലാടട ദ നടന്മ-നമ0൭.
Young master, one day, you will be king.
വധ സ്വദ, ടവദ്ധ ഘി നല്സി, ഡേോമിത്ഥ നല! ന്മ.
Then you can chase those slobbering, mangy, stupid poachers
[ലാട ഡ മഴമിലാംല്‍സിഭ്യല 0൭൦0ലല൦0 ൩ ാധഡിപാലിവ്ലാ ൭0 0ഠഠ്൦ബ
from dawn until dusk.
ച്ചി ടധാധി ബാല ടു.
Hey, Uncle Scar! Guess what?
ലല, ലിലി നല്ധ ലിന
I despise guessing games.
ലച്% ലിധാിത്ന ട൭-ല0.
I'm gonna be King of Pride Rock.
മയ മിതി ല്യം 7൫5൨0 ൧0൦5.
Oh, goody!
വ്പാമറ്ധടില്വ്‌
My dad just showed me the whole kingdom,
൧൭1൨ ടര ചിന്ന 11 1:11
and I'm gonna rule it all!
ഠി ട്ര ത്ഥ നനലന്മ്നിഭടന്ധസര!
Yes. Well, forgive me for not leaping for joy.
വ ഴിടലിംവിതിദധാല്റിം 1൭ നലിംന്വാമ ഷന ഭന്പമ൨.
Bad back, you know.
ഗിലറ്ധസില൨, ടപന്വാലല്ഖ.
Hey, Uncle Scar.
ലല, ൧ഥലിടല്ചേ.
When I'm king, what'll that make you?
൧്യാദ്ധിട ട്ര ഒഠി। 7൭9, 091 ലിറ്ധിട നേന നമ്മ?
A monkey's uncle.
ലിശ്യധ്ധാലഡിം
-You're so weird. -You have no idea.
൧൭ ലിബി 0൭104. ലാലാല യലലഘാവിത്ഥ.
So, your father showed you the whole kingdom, did he?
1111111111 71 ടലധഡ്നിഭഘ്യ ബ്‌?
Everything.
ലേദ്ബുയ.
He didn't show you what's beyond that rise at the northern border?
൧9 150ഡബുധിഠത്ഥ ലാട ഠി ടലാട!॥£ 10൫200 ഠ ടന്പാടഠ് ധ്യ ഡ?
Well, no. He said I can't go there.
1ദിധാബ്ര ടര ഖഥംബിഭ ട൭൫9.
And he's absolutely right.
ഴിനനമന്ാാബി തബ.
It's far too dangerous.
1 നലില്ധ ാദ്൭.
Only the bravest lions go there.
ബു ടിനാരന ദിനാ ലാല്‌ 0ഠില്വ്വായ! ൫ ടന൭.
Well, I'm brave. What's out there?
മുതാധ്സാന്്. ൧ഠ9 വാട ഠി ടന്മ്‌?
I'm sorry, Simba, I just can't tell you.
[ഴീടല്‌, 51സ്വാഒ, 09 ലിറവ്ലിവാംില്ഡാലന്ല്ഡ.
Why not?
(൭റ്വാ ധി?
I'm only looking out for the well-being of my favorite nephew.
ല്ലി ഥന നിനത്ഥശ്ധാലിത്ഥ നേ ദ്ധ ഭടദനാണാലറഥിം
Yeah, right! I'm your only nephew.
വല്ല്യ! ചേരി ടദ്ധ-ടാഡസുയ നല ടാ്ധാലട ലാമി
All the more reason for me to be protective.
[മദാ ധിാദ്ധ നനാ! യല.
An elephant graveyard is no place for a young prince. Oops!
102൨ ൧ലിഡാഥമന ല്യല്വാധിത്ബ്ല 1ലന്വാമ ധന്ധിലാധ്ടെ സ്വഠ്ദ. ഷ്ണ
An elephant what? Whoa!
10൭൨ ലാ? ഗ്‌
Oh, dear, I've said too much.
൧ഠ്ധിന്ി, 0510 ഥി ലിലാദട ലവ്ഭ്വാ.
Well, l suppose you'd have found out sooner or later,
ലാ, ്വാദ്ധദ്ധാടടി ഡേ ലിത്ഥ ദ്വ ല്ഡ്്ധാട,
you being so clever and all.
നനമറഠ്ഘാത്ഥ മ്മി ലം
Just do me one favor.
ധന ടബ ടല ലാല്ന്ന്മ വാലി
Promise me you'll never visit that dreadful place.
ദല്ുദല്വില്സുത്നാ ലിനിറത്ന ഥലി ൭ ന്ദ്‌ ബിഗ്ധ.
No problem.
1199 നടി.
There's a good lad.
ധിട്വാധഠ്ട്വന ലിം
You run along now and have fun.
ലവ ലയില്വാലടല
it's our little secret.
ബി ലിം സ്മ !ന്മവാല്ധമ.
-Hey, Nala. -Hi, Simba.
ലി, ൪൭19. 1, ട1സ്ാഒ.
Come on. I just heard about this great place.
൦൬൩. ദുര ലഠ്ലബോല ന്നാ ട്വ വ്വ ഘാല്‌.
Simba! I'm kind of in the middle of a bath.
ന്നാ! (൧ ടര ടാ ന്നാല്‍.
And it's time for yours.
ലിന യല ദ്ദ.
Mom!
[ഗി
Mom, you're messing up my mane!
ഗിലപവടഥില്വാധ്ധ ഘോവയിം മര നന!
Okay, okay, I'm clean. Can we go now?
ര്യ, റിയു, ടര ഠ്ദ്വാലടി. 8൩ ഹായ ടല?
So, where are we going?
ട്ഒഠി।, 09 നല്ലിഭ നട ബി?
It better not be anyplace dumb.
ല്വാഘ്ഘ്വാ 19 0ധിത്ഥ ന്ദ്ര 0൦59൨.
No, it's really cool.
11ഠ്മിലദ നനന ലാട.
So, where is this really cool place?
പഠി, ഠി നന്നു ല്ല ലായ?
-Around the water hole. -The water hole?
-8ലഠിലയ് ഠബോദിധാല 1. ഥാ ചന?
What's so great about the water hole?
യാന ഘാഖ ടാ ഠി ധാ ലസ?
I'll show you when we get there.
൧്യാദ്ധിട ൭൨ ടാന്വാമി ൩൯ ടര മ്രാല.
Mom, can I go with Simba?
[ഗിമിപാഠില്‍ ടമുയിവ്‌ ല്സാ?
What do you think, Sarabi?
൧്വാ3 ലാല്ല ധം, ലഖ്‌?
Well...
മൃ 953...
-Please?
-8ഠിലന
It's all right with me.
ഗ്ലിധല്ധടം.
-Yeah! -All right!
ലിവ്‌
As long as Zazu goes with you.
കടിയ 2ദമ്ധ ലാവ്‌ ടലല്‍യി!.
No, not Zazu.
1: 2:12711:151
Step lively.
പട്ടി ലോക്‌ ട॥൪.
The sooner we get to the water hole, the sooner we can leave.
1൭൮! ലോദ്ധിന്മ മാട ഠി ധാ ല്ന്ധ, 1൭9] ല്രോ1ന്മാഠിലല്‍ ധി.
So, where are we really going?
പഠി, ടലാനാസര ന്മ നലിലഭ നന ബ്‌?
An elephant graveyard.
(൭ നമ൩വാലിഡാഥനാല്ന.
Wow!
ഠ്‌
Zazu.
മമ.
Right. So, how are we gonna ditch the dodo?
ലി ഠി, ാാവ്നടന്മ റമ ൩൫൭൫ 11:11 1011-11
Just look at you two.
1൦100 ഴയ്ലിവാല്ധട ല്‍.
Little seeds of romance blossoming in the savanna.
പൂചന്വാലിസുയാധ-ധനാദ ണ്ട 9൭0 സ്ധിദ നല്‌ ഠ। ടമ.
Your parents will be thrilled,
ധാ യാടി ിവ്ഥ ഡ്മ,
what with your being betrothed and all.
നനമറഠ്യാത്ഥ മമ്ലാല്ധദ ട്വാബ്ധനമ.
Be-what?
ലലാ?
Betrothed. Intended.
ദല്ധനാനാ. ൧൮൦ഠ൦ബിത്ഥ.
Affianced.
൧0ല്ധാത്ഥ.
Meaning...
ഗിലിദ്ധാസുയ...
One day, you two are going to be married.
ട്വ ലി ൩, ഡേോ്ലാല്ധാ മിത ഥാലിവിയ്ന.
Yuck!
ലസ!
I can't marry her. She's my friend.
[ഗാല ടര നഹാടയ്ബ്സര. 8:11 1-1
Yeah, it'd be so weird.
പ്ല, നമന൯ 0൦॥1ലാധില്യദഠ്സുയ.
Sorry to bust your bubble,
ഗി ഘന നല്യടഠലിത്ഥ മലം,
but you two turtle doves have no choice.
1 യ്ിവാല്ധട വ3ഠ്9 01110.
It's a tradition going back generations.
ബി ഠിടി വ്വ ്ലാഡസബിത്ഥ ടല്ദ്ധാലുലലമട। നബ.
When I'm king, that'll be the first thing to go.
്യാദ്ധിട ടഖരദഠി। ലയ, ധിമി ഗലിത്ഥ ലാറ ത്ഥ ഠ॥ഘ്വഥധടിത്ന.
-Not so long as I'm around. -Well, in that case, you're fired.
1191 ടലഠി ട്ര നട വോ. (ദ്ധി, യി ിവാടല്‌.
Nice try, but only the king can do that.
്ോോദബുത്നാ ലിപി! മസ ഭ്ം ന ാഠില്വാധദ്ലാല്വ്വ.
Well, he's the future king.
ലവ, 19 0൭1൭] നബുദഠി। 7൭൭.
Yeah, so you have to do what I tell you.
൭,൮90 ബ്യലാല്ധിവഡ്‌ ഖ്പിത്വാ ടര.
Not yet, I don't.
ദല്ധന 1.
And with an attitude like that,
ഉലഹുബാലമല വ ടലാല്വ്ധ,
I'm afraid you're shaping up to be a pretty pathetic king, indeed.
നന്വാല്സമ മ്മില്‍! നബി 9൮൭൫൭ 1൭൦5൦0൧൭൦൨.
Not the way I see it.
മയ 1മഗമടാല്വ്വ.
I'm gonna be a mighty king
൧൮ ഒഷ്ഥ ൭൨ ൭(൭)൭൨റു ഒറു
So enemies beware
പ്ഒധ്‌ ൧൭൧൭റ൭-(9റ ൭൧ 1൭൧0൭7 ല്ലേ
Well, I've never seen a king of beasts
ലഗ്ന ഥാലഗ ഒ 0൭ 7൭൭9 ഗഗ
With quite so little hair
൭൧൮ ൭ഥലെഷ൭ഥഥ്ഥ
I'm gonna be the main event
൧൮ ഒഷ്ഥ ൭൨ (ഒസകഥ ഗ്ന
Like no king was before
2 ലാഗ്‌ ഗലാഒ! റ്൭7 ൭( )൭൧0 ലോല
I'm brushin' up on lookin' down
൧൮ഥല൭൧ഗ ഗഥ്ഥഥെറ്ടെററ (ഭ ഗഗ
I'm workin' on my roar
൧ ഥല്‌ ഗധ്ലനെറ്ുദഗ്നേ
Thus far, a rather uninspiring thing
ടല൭൪൭॥ ൨, ഒ:ഥ നട ഒല്ലഡ്ഭ
Oh, I just can't wait to be king
൨൧൧, ൭൧ ൭ ക്ല സന ല്വടവ്‌ 7൭൭
You've rather a long way to go, young master, if you think...
[ഗിമടിവയദധിറാലുല്ന്മഥ യം, വറ സ്ധഠ്ട, യ്ദ്ധ മ്മി...
-No one sayin’, "Do this" -Now, when ! said that...
- 7൭ഠ്൭ 549൧൭ (൭(൭, "29% റ്റ്‌" -൪൧൭൧൭ 5ഒ൭)൭ (൭൭ ൧൧...
-No one saying, "Be there" -What I meant was...
- 7ഒ൭ഠ്൭ 549൧൭ ൭(൭, "ലസ്സ്‌ ഗദ" പിഒ 5൭൭...
-No one sayin’, "Stop that" -You don't realize...
- 7൭ഠ്൭ 549൧൭ (൭(൭, പറ്റണ 2ല്സ്ഥ്‌ -41൭:ല൭ ൭റെ൭...
-No one sayin’, "See here" -Now, see here!
- 7ഒ൭ഠ്ദ 549൧൭ 4൭(൭, "൧ ൦െറ്റട7 ഒ" -ക്ലര൭൧റു, റ്റു 5൧7
Free to run around all day
ലാട ാലഒ7്‌ (൭ നഥട ൧൭
Well, that's definitely out.
പ്‌ ലഭ്വാ.
Free to do it all my way
8ലാടട ാലഗറ്ല നെറ്റ്‌ ഗ്രേ
[think it's time that you and!
൧൭5൭൧)൭ റ ൧൭9 ൩൭൭൭ ഗ്൭
Arranged a heart-to-heart
28ലഥഥഗറ്റ റ്‌്‌ ഗല (൭ ഗദ
Kings don't need advice
൭൭ 4൭:ഥല്ലക്ഥ 0൭൭൧൭
From little hornbills for a start
7ലഥ്ഒനറ)൭ റ്൭7്ഥടറ്ട ഗഥഥറ്റ ററ
If this is where the monarchy is headed
ര൭(ദഥ ൧ഗ ഒ൭൧ഗ ൭൧ (ലടഒഒ ൧൨
Count me out
284൭7൭7 ടഒ)൭ ലസ്സ്‌
Out of service, out of Africa
ലന ൧൭, (൭൧൭൦ റ്൭7്‌ ൧7൩൪
! wouldn't hang about
൭൭൮൭ ഒഗക്ഥ (ക൭ വ്‌ 5൧
This child is getting wildly out of wing
280൭൦7 ലേഒഗ 7൦9൨-9൨ ഗദനഥാലഗ)ട
Oh, I just can't wait to be king
൨൧൧, ൭൧ ൭ ക്ല സന ല്വടവ്‌ 7൭൭
Everybody, look left
കലനഥ൭, ൧ഥറ്ഒറററ 7ഗ7്‌
Everybody, look right
കല ഥ൭, ൧൭ഥറ്ഒഗറ (ഒഥഥ
Everywhere you look, I'm
൧ഒഥറ്ടറഒഗ (൭ നഥട ൧൭
Standing in the spotlight
൧൮ ഒഷ്ഥ ൭൨൪ ൧ല൩൭7൭൨
Not yet!
ഒല്ധന ഠാ!
Let every creature go for broke and sing
84൭7൭7 ടലനഥട ഗ7൭:ഗ൧ 7൧൮൭൧൦ “ലാല 7൧൭
Let's hear it in the herd and on the wing
൧റെറ്റട7്ക്ഥ'ണ റ്റ (കനറ റ ;ഖഠനഥഠവ്ഥറ്ട
It's gonna be King Simba's finest fling
൧൧൭൧ (വലാടഒഥ ജദ്ഒ ാദുക്ഥറ “ലഗടനട
Oh, I just can't wait to be king
൨൧൧, ൭൧ ൭ ക്ല സന ല്വടവ്‌ 7൭൭
Oh, I just can't wait
റ, ഒ൧൭ 5൧൭൦
To be king
൭൮൭൨ 7൭൭
Il beg your pardon, madam, but
[ഗിന്ഠ നാല്‌, ധന, ല്വാി
get off!
1ഠഠ്റാനാഥല്‍്‌
Simba?
ടന്ധാമ?
Nala!
പിഒ!
All right! It worked!
മമറ്റ്ട! ധാടബാല്മട॥!
-We lost him. -lam a genius.
19 0ല)ദ്വര നലിട്ഹിത്ഥ 910. ദ്യ നനാ 01൦
Hey, genius, it was my idea.
ലല, ടാ്വമിപ്ധ ഠേ ടര.
Yeah, but I pulled it off.
ല്ല ടര ൭ നബുദരി്ഖസ്സമ.
-With me! -Yeah?
ലട ടര! നിത?
-Pinned ya. -Hey, let me up!
ദ്യ നല. ലി, ലാദടിത്ഥ ട്ര!
Pinned ya again.
മയ നന്മ.
This is it. We made it.
ബില ന്വാസഭ. ഗ്൭ 1 ടന്വാല്‌.
Whoa!
മവ
It's really creepy.
1൭ നന്മ നസബഘിത്ല.
Yeah.
വ.
Isn't it great?
ല്ലാണിത്ന്‌?
-We could get in big trouble. -l know!
19 സ്ധ്ിന്൩ ലത ബിം മദര ദ്ധി
l wonder if its brains are still in there.
നല ടന ദ ദസ നടടി മഠ ഠി ലിന.
There's only one way to know.
റബ ടല ധന്ധിറ്ല്ാഖിത്യ്ാന്സുയ.
Come on, let's go check it out.
൧൮, നല ന്൫ 0ലഠ ൦.
Wrong! The only checking out you will do will be to check out of here.
ലവ്‌ ടംബ-ടദ്ധസര ന്ദി ദിത്൩ ലാല ലിനിഭ്ധല കി ട്ബ.
Oh, man!
ഒട!
We're way beyond the boundary of the Pride Lands.
൭ ഠ്ല്വാജഠ്ട [ധന ഠി വധ ടല്വാദഠ് 1൫൭൨0 ൧0൦6.
Look, banana beak is scared.
1൦10൭0, ടരാധസഡനാ ധന ദ്ല്വല്ഡ.
It's Mr. banana beak to you, fuzzy,
ദ്രന്ധില ടി ധസ്ഥ ാധന്ലി, ടി ധ്ധിലാട
and right now we are all in very real danger.
0 ടല്വഷ്വനാ ന്൯ ടന്ധഃ ലാ ഠാ.
Danger?
പ്ര?
l walk on the wild side.
മയ നന ടിയി ലോല.
I laugh in the face of danger.
മയ ിര് ദ്വാലാ॥ിാലടടന്ധിര ലാല്‌.
Well, well, well, Banzai, what have we got here?
1൦1050, 8ന്മി, ട്രാ ൮൭൧ ന്൯ ഠ്വ ല്‌?
I don't know, Shenzi.
5ബ്ല്വില, ടഘബ്ഷ്‌.
What do you think, Ed?
൧്വാ3ലാലിട്വാമ ധം, £ഠ7
Just what I was thinking.
മുത ാഥ മടല്‍.
Atrio of trespassers!
൭ 0ല0ലഘാ്വാബാദ!
And quite by accident, let me assure you.
ദ്വി 151 ടലൃല്യമ, ഗല മ്വേമില ത്വാ ടമ.
A simple navigational error.
ല്ല ട്ടി 5൭൨.
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
പസി, നി, ലസി.
I know you. You're Mufasa's little stooge.
മയ ഭി ലിം ൧ഷഘിലന്മഠ്ട ട്ട.
I], madam, am the king's major-domo.
മയ, 000, ദ വാലധബട 0൭ അ.
And that would make you...
ഗിലിദ്ധാസ്ുയ യല്ല...
The future king.
8 7൭9.
Do you know what we do to kings who step out of their kingdom?
ല്ഡ ലായി ൧൨൭ നന്മഠ്ല്ോ ദ്വ ഠി ധ്യാന നലലത?
You can't do anything to me.
ഡിം ഖമ ഖ്വാമ-ദ്വാദ വാദ ട൭.
Technically, they can. We are on their land.
ലോലസ്ുയ, ൧൦16. ഗലാ ഠി മഡട് നലിയ.
But you told me they're nothing but slobbering, mangy, stupid poachers.
വല്യ മഴമറ നലട്ര ബുദ്ധ്‌ 0൦00ല്‍ ൮൭൬൭ ലലിവ്വാ ൩0൦9൦൨.
Ix-nay on the upid-stay.
പ്ാബ്മ൨ ടലാഥ്ലാലിയ്ദന 0ഠഠ൦൨.
-Who are you callin’ upid-stay? -My, my, my. Look at the sun!
ഡമി ടില്വാുയനാ ൦൦ന്‌ കിണ്ടി ലം നമ്ല്മ്ഥ യി!
-It's time to go! -What's the hurry?
പ്‌ഗ്ടട ധന്ധിലാലി!! -1(൭0ല്വാട 'റുടടദ-റടട ടന്ന
We'd love you to stick around for dinner.
ഗിംി0 നല്ത്ഥ നടന ലാലടാണട യി.
Yeah, we could have whatever's lion around!
൭, ാില്വില്വന്ദ നല്ത്ഥ ദ്വാമ-്വാദ ൮൭ ലഠ്ന്വാല ഠി ടലി!
Wait, wait, wait, 1 got one, I got one!
പസി, ൩, ട്ര വാധന ഠ്ട ട്ഡ!
Make mine a cub sandwich! Whaddaya think?
ദലലിത്ഥ ടര ടവ ടാനാധം ഡാലി ൧്വാ3ലാലിട്വാമ ബ്ല
What, Ed? What is it?
൧്വാ, ഠി? ചലല?
Hey, did we order this dinner to go?
ലി, 9 സന്ദ നമിത നമി ന്മ ്ാഥാവവടിത്ന്‌
No, why?
11ഠ്ടിലഭന്വാദ്‌?
‘Cause there it goes!
ലോല്വ ദ ഠ്ട്വ്വാലയ!!
-Did we lose 'em? -I think so.
ഗല 0 ി്ല്ത്ന? ടു ാല്റ്ധ.
Where's Zazu?
ക്മമ്ധ ഠി നന്മ?
The little major-domo bird hippety-hopped
൭ ലാധസനാ ലഡ്ൃഥസടട്ടന്മ 000 നല്‍൦0൧൭-1൦൫൧൭
all the way to the birdie-boiler.
വന്ാമില ട്വ ഭവാലംസ്ലലാധസന.
No! Not the birdie-boiler!
1 ടര മണ്ഡ ലാല്ല!
Hey, why don't you pick on somebody your own size?
ല്‍, ഭറ്വാ യിലി ോദസനാ ടന ദന മലി
-Like you? -Oops.
ലാല ബ്ല കിണി
Boo!
ലിറ
Simba!
ന്നാ!
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
ഗി, നലി, നടി, ടി ല്ലവണ.
That was it?
വ ടദ്യദ്‌?
Do it again. Come on.
ദ്ധി ടര ൭1. ൧൮൨.
-Please, please! Uncle, uncle! -Silence!
ഠി, ൩ നസബ്ഘട്ല്‍്‌ ണ്‌!
-We're gonna shut up right now! -Calm down. We're really sorry.
രി ലിത്ഥന്ധ്ധാ സ്ധിഥ്‌ ട്രാ! ലമ. ബി സ്പ നട്‌.
If you ever come near my son again...
ദരിദ്ധിഖ്സ്ധ ലമി നിലയി മന്മ്ലാടെ 11...
-Your son. -Did you know that?
൧0൭10 മധ്യ ഗമിവല്ഡ ലിറ
No. Me? I didn't know... No, did you?
1൦ ടര? പര ചറല്ഡ. ഡലി്ലാധ്മ?
-No, of course not. -No.
19 ടവഠില (ടന്ധ ഠി. [91൦
Ed?
ഠി
Toodles.
൭.
-Dad, I... -You deliberately disobeyed me.
൮൭, ടര... ഗാ ല്ല നായി ഗ്മ ഷത്വ.
-Dad, I'm... I'm sorry. -Let's go home.
൧൮൭, നലീത്ഥ ടര. ച്ഗ്॥ി 09 ാധിടനാ.
Il thought you were very brave.
മയ ടടാ യി ടണല്‍ ൦.
Zazu.
മമ.
Yes, sire?
൭, ഡബ്വ?
Take Nala home. I've got to teach my son a lesson.
മദ പലിട ധി. മുതാല്ധ ല്യം ലട.
Come, Nala.
ഥീ, 919.
Simba, good luck.
ന്നാ, ടന ലാലു.
Simba!
ന്നാ!
Simba, I'm very disappointed in you.
ന്ധ, ക൭൯ ണോ ലോ യം
-l know. -You could've been killed.
ട്ര ഖ്്ഡ. ഗി സ്ധനഘാന്ന ലലാധസ്ധ്ഒഠ.
You deliberately disobeyed me,
11111111
and what's worse, you put Nala in danger.
നിലാ ബിലിടാ।, ഡേോ്ഗസ്ധഡ്‌ നമ്പാഖമരിത് സധപ.
l was just trying to be brave, like you.
മയ ഡേനട നല്ലു വാന്്ബി, നേന ൧൮൭1൨.
I'm only brave when I have to be.
൧൭1൨ ഡാലി ല്വാഖ്ധ॥ദ ലാല.
Simba, being brave
ന്ധ, നബുദഠി। ല്ലി
doesn't mean you go looking for trouble.
191 ടനടട്വസ്മാല്നലന്മ ഡേയ്ലാലി നന്മ ടട.
But you're not scared of anything.
ലവ കമ ലവമിഡത്ഥ ല്വാ-ല്വാ ലാന.
l was today.
ഷുര്്വാലടടാ 1൭൮൭൦.
-You were? -Yes.
ഒല്ധിത്്ന? 9.
l thought I might lose you.
ഷുഖ്വഷര ച്ര്ഥിഭ്വിദ്ുന മലം
I guess even kings get scared, huh?
പന്ഥാ ദ്യ ഥന 0ഠിലവാലമടദ പവത്‌?
-But you know what? -What?
ല്യാി 1മിഡ ലിഗല്വാട? വാമ?
I think those hyenas were even scareder.
മട സു ഠ്ധാധിറാധാധ്റഠി ലടടട്ട്ധ്നിലാ ട്വ.
‘Cause nobody messes with your dad.
ലോല്വ ഠി ടില്വാമ ലി ദ ലാട! ലോന ഷ്യ യല
-Come here, you. -No! No!
പ്ഗീി ട്വ. പ്രാ! പബ്‌
Come here!
ഗി ടബ്‌!
Gotcha!
ഉല്ല
Dad?
ഷുഖ്്ന
-We're pals, right? -Right.
9 യധബാലിപത്ഥ? 9.
And we'll always be together, right?
ഉബാദ ടിത്ഥ ടബസിടടട്പാല്ടനണട, ദന?
Simba, let me tell you something that my father told me.
ന്നാ, 01൮ ത്വാന്ല്ഡ ടട 0൭൦൬൭൨ ഠിലേന്മിത്ഥ ഠില്വാല്യാ ൧൮൭1൨.
Look at the stars.
“1ല്ഠംറ്വാസ്നാ-സ്നാ വധ.
The great kings of the past look down on us from those stars.
ല്യം ലാട ഠി നട ടിന നനലിയലിത്ിന്മ ഠ്‌ ടന.
-Really? -Yes.
ഒല്ധിത്്ന? 9.
So whenever you feel alone,
പഠി ടലില്വാ ൭ ്ലിവാടടം ഭടധസ്ിന,
just remember that those kings will always be there to guide you.
റഖില്വാംമ ല്ല ല്ത്ഥ ടലസിദടദ നലമ്പാലിത്ഥ മഴമിലാറ്ധന.
And so will I.
ഉ ാല്റ്ധ്മ കര.
Man, that lousy Mufasa. l won't be able to sit for a week.
ടിയ, ടി ിധ്ടടാ വ. മുര 1൭10൭0 ്ധറ്ധി ടലടടദ ടലദണട ട്സ്ാാധ.
It's not funny, Ed.
[1-111-15
Hey, shut up!
ലി, ഠി ണില്വ
Will you knock it off?
8ഠ1ല ഴ്ലിവാല്ധമ ലിസ്ാധണ്പാാധ?
-Well, he started it. -Look at you guys.
൧ നടന്ധില്ഖ്സര. - ൭൦10൭0 യ ടന്ധമ.
No wonder we're dangling at the bottom of the food chain.
ലപ്്ധിംവിന്ദ ലാമ ഠി ാഹാസ്വഥനാ നല നിത.
Man, I hate dangling.
8 ലാബി.
Yeah? If it weren't for those lions, we'd be runnin’ the joint.
ദരിദ്ധധാധിത്ിഭന്ട ട്നാ-ടനാ ൮, ന 501 നനഘ്ാധടലി യ്യാടന ബ്‌.
Man, I hate lions.
മുയാലിത്ഥ ടിന.
-So pushy. -And hairy.
ലിയ നനോടടലം ൧0 ലാവ.
-And stinky. -And, man, are they...
൧0 ്ധടധി ൧൩, ൭9൨1൨, നട ണന...
Ugly!
0ഠഠ൦ല്‍
Surely we lions are not all that bad.
ല്ധസ്ര ബി ടന 14 ടലബിഗ്ധ.
Scar. It's just you.
ലല. ഡമി്വാസര.
We were afraid it was somebody important.
വി നഎഉ്ത്ഥ 19 ടട നാന സ്ഥ.
Yeah, you know, like Mufasa.
പല്ലി, ടലാപസ ഴീധ്ടടമ.
-Yeah. -l see.
9. വാല്ധ.
-Now that's power! -Tell me about it.
ധിട്നിവടട! പ്‌ഗീനമറ്റ ലാബി.
I just hear that name and I shudder.
ലോധ ടല നസ ട്ര 911 നലഡ്യാല്‍ല്ല.
-Mufasa! -Do it again.
പ്ഗ്ഥ്ഒടമ! ധി.
Mufasa!
ഗ്ധ്ടട!
Mufasa! Mufasa! Mufasa!
ഗിധ്ടടം! ്ഥ്ദട! ഴിധ്ടട!
It tingles me.
9 0൨൭ ടര ഗുസ്ധബ.
I'm surrounded by idiots.
മയ നാടി.
Now, you, Scar, l mean, you're one of us. mean, you're our pal.
൧ഡഘില്ാധിദ, ടല, യി ലാമി ി്വാമാദ ൭൩. ഡി ലിത്നിയി.
Charmed.
ദനാ സ൭.
I like that. He's not king, but he's still so proper.
മയ ടിയു. ഥിാധിത്ഥ ത്വ, വാ ഠി ലാല്ഡലാല്ധാ।വാടമട.
Yeah. Hey, did you bring us anything to eat,
൭. 061, മഗലിറഠിട ഗെ നലിദ്ഥറ ധന്ധിവഷ്ി,
Scar, old buddy, old pal? Huh? Did ya, did ya, did ya?
ലേ, ടി യി ണട്‌? [1-111-11
I don't think you really deserve this.
മയ മമ യ്ലിദതി്നലലനമുയ.
I practically gift-wrapped those cubs for you,
മുര ഠ്വ ലല്ല യ ഠി ഠില്ാന ന്ദ യം,
and you couldn't even dispose of them.
യാ വ ധന യല നന്വാധാഥസ്ധ.
Well, you know, it wasn't exactly like they was alone, Scar.
ലവ, ധ്യ നലലത ാലടലറി(, ടല.
Yeah. What were we supposed to do?
൭. ല്യാ്നഠ്ഡിയ് ധന
Kill Mufasa?
ദ്ധന്ധ്വ്ഴിധ്ടട?
Precisely.
ലാമ ടലയി!.
! know that your powers of retention
൧൮ (൭൧൧ റ്ട൭ ഗുദ
Are as wet as a warthog's backside
ക്ലല70൭൧ ാഗറ്ററുഗറ്റ ൧2൧ ഗഥ്റെ
But thick as you are, pay attention
7ഒ൧! ലാല; റ്ഗനനഥ, റ്റു ക്ഥയ
My words are a matter of pride
൭൭-൪൭൧ ഒറ്997 ന ഒഡഗധ
It's clear from your vacant expressions
പ്ലഒട റ്‌ ൭൧ നഥനഥ കഥ ഒഥലഡധലടടടട
The lights are not all on upstairs
൭൧ ഥഥക്ഥ ടഗെററ)ഷ൨ഥററ ഥററ്ല്‌
But we're talking kings and successions
7ഒ൧ ൧49 ലാഗ്‌ 4റെഒററ്റ (ഖഗ്൭ റ (ഖലഘടഒറ
Even you can't be caught unawares
൧൧൮൪൭൧ ൭൧൧൦ 4ഒഥലട്ട
So prepare for the chance of a lifetime
28ലടവെ൭ഒഗ ഥ്‌ ൧൭൧൭൧ ലണഥ7 റ്ഥാ
Be prepared for sensational news
8ലടവെ൭ഒ൧ഗ ൧ഥഥ്ഥാലഗ്ഒ 4“ലഗനദെറ്റട?
A shiny new era is tiptoeing nearer
ലഭൃഷ്ഥ്ു ലനഒഥറ ഒകഥ (ധ൧ഥ൮൧ ൧൧൭
And where do we feature?
൭൩ ൧൧൭ വ്‌ നദ?
Just listen to teacher
൧റെറ്റട7 ലയ ദക്ഥ ടട
! know it sounds sordid
ഗ്ഗഥാഥഗ്വക കട
But you'll be rewarded
7ഒഥ൧ഒട൭നഥ ക്ഥ റ്ഥ൭ഒട
When at last 1 am given my dues
൧൭൧9 ഒഗ൧ണ൭ :൧ റ്ദ്ാദ൭! ഗഗ
And injustice deliciously squared
൧൭൦ (൭ഠഒ൪൭൨൭൧ ട5ഥ്രഗ്ഒഥ൭ വ്ഥ൧൭൭൭5
Be prepared
ലട വ്ഒ'ഒ7
Yeah, be prepared. We'll be prepared. For what?
൮൭, ാലടടഠിഒ. ദ്വി മത ഥാലടലഠിദ. വന്ധില്വാ?
For the death of the king.
പന്ധിലിഭനബാതയ്ദ ഭ്വംന്൫.
-Why, is he sick? -No, fool, we're going to kill him.
1(൭0ല്വാഃ, ഠി ടലിനിത്ന? -8ലി0, 00901, 1019 മിയ്വാധസ്ധ ഠിഒ.
-And Simba, too. -Great idea. Who needs a king?
-ടമ്പാമ, ധാമ. ഠി നാമ ടല ലിധിത്ഥ യമ?
No king, no king
74ഒ9റ9 7ല൭, 7ഒറ്9 7൭൭
-Idiots! There will be a king! -Hey, but you said...
-8ഠഠിഠ൮൨ ല്യം നടി ട്ട! ലി, 1ഖ്വാ1 യ്ലിലിത്...
I will be king!
മയ മിതി ദ്യ!
Stick with me,
൭0൦1൭൨ ടര,
and you'll never go hungry again.
൦ യി ടല്ധഃ ഖഠത്ലില്യാ മ.
-Yeah! All right! -Long live the king!
൭ ഒമ്ടിദ്ല്‍ ദ്ധി ഡബ്വ!
Long live the king! Long live the king!
ഉദ്ധിമഡാബ്വ! ദ്ധിഡധബ്വ്‌
It's great that we'll soon be connected
൧(൭൧റ൮ക൭൧ 2൭0൮൧൨൮൭ 4ഗ്൭ ഒ൭രഥ 2ലടദഥറ്ട
With a king who'll be all-time adored
൧ഥുറെറ്റണ 7൭൭ )൭൨റ്ു ഒക്ഥ ലെന) ട ടഒഥഗന7്‌
Of course, quid pro quo you're expected
ക്ഥഠ്ഒഗ 4ഒറ൧, ലോദഒറ്റഖ്‌ ൧2൭'ഒ5൭൧, ൭൧ വണട
To take certain duties on board
ഗ്രഗഥ്ലനഡെഒ൭ഥകഥ 4൧09 )൭ഥറ റ്ഥണ്‌
The future is littered with prizes
0ഒട൭ റ്ല്ാ്ഹ വ്വാഥഥ്സ്‌ ൧ഒഥ)൭ഗദ്ഥഥറ
And though I'm the main addressee
14ഒ(൭൧൧ ൭:ഥ൭൦ഗ ൧ഥലനസ്നട ശ്ന ഥ)൭
The point that l must emphasize is
൧൧9 )൭൧ഥറ ഥലവഥ (ധ ലവ
You won't get a sniff without me!
7ഒഗ്ഥാഡ (കഥ (ഒഗഥ റ്ദ്രാദ! ഒഥഒ-ഒല൧൭!
So prepare for the coup of the century
28ലടവെ൭ഒഗ ഥ്‌ ൧൦റഗഒറദ[ഒറ (ലഗഥെട! ഒ൭7 ൨
Be prepared for the murkiest scam
28ല5വെ൭ഒ൧7 ഥ്‌ ഥല്വാഥറെ (ലാഥഡഥ
Meticulous planning
൧ലദറഠറ്റ 7ഒ൧
Tenacity spanning
ഒല 7097
Decades of denial
28ലഡ്ലരറ്‌ (൧ രെ
ls simply why I'll be king undisputed
4ധണ൦ ലോദ്ഥവട (ധ കഥ നഖ്‌ ൭൭
Respected, saluted
൧70൧൩൭൧, റ്വാഥ്്‌ഒ
And seen for the wonder! am
൧൭ (കഥ! വ്ഘലസ്നദ റ്റ
Yes, my teeth and ambitions are bared
൭, ഗവ റ ഡ്൭-ഡ്ഖഡ ലല്‌
Be prepared
ലട വ്ഒ'ഒ7
Yes, our teeth and ambitions are bared
൭, (൭70 റ്റ വ്ഒ-ല്൭ (൭൩ “ലല
You wait here. Your father has a marvelous surprise for you.
ഡി ൦ ടബ്‌. ഷി മിറ ഷ്യധ്ബുത്നാ ലാട ധസ്ധിമയലിം
What is it?
൧്വാഘ്വ്്സയ്‌?
If l told you, it wouldn't be a surprise now, would it?
ദ്രിദ്ധവാമധിവാല്ല്ഡ,।ാധിത്ി! ട്വ ഷ്യ, ധിരന?
If you tell me, I'll still act surprised.
ദ്രിദ്ധവാമധിഥലിത്വാ, ടര മിരബാധമ്പാധാലര്ഥ്‌.
You are such a naughty boy.
൧ഡിണനണനനാ ധഠ്ല്വന നത.
-Come on, Uncle Scar. -No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
ലാബില്‍, ലലല. - ടിധാഠിലല്‍, മ൦1൦൨, ഒവാഠ൦.
This is just for you and your daddy.
വി മസ നല യി മതി മലം
You know, a sort of father-son thing.
[ഗിലറ്ധസി൭൨, ഹാലിന്മി ലാട ഒ നലം
Well, I'd better go get him.
[ലിവാലിലാപ്ധിറഥാലയി യാ! ഠി.
-I'll go with you. -No.
ദ്യ നലിയ. പ്ല.
No. Just stay on this rock.
പ്‌. ഗവഠ്ധി മട ദ്ധ ബ്‌ ഠിദണ-ഠന.
You wouldn't want to end up in another mess
ദിന യിലി! ഗലിട്ധ ധിം
like you did with the hyenas.
ടല്ലാല്‌ !ഷ്യദഠിദ ന്വാ൦ന്ലി ലോറ ഠ്ധാധിഡ.
-You know about that? -Simba, everybody knows about that.
൧൭ ലിവല്ഡ ന്നാ ധ്ധ? -ടമ്പാഃ, ട്വ മല ലധനല്ഡ.
-Really? -Yes.
ഒല്ധിത്്ന? 9.
Lucky daddy was there to save you, eh?
പടട ലിയ ട്വ നനസഭദന്ത്ഥ യ്ലിപത്ന?
And just between us,
:11:1:1 1-111-11
you might want to work on that little roar of yours, hmm?
ട്രാ ൪൭ യിലാ നാദ്ധനന ഭം ലിഡ്‌?
Okay.
ര്യം.
Hey, Uncle Scar, willl like this surprise?
ലല, ൧ ഥലിടലേ, ദയ ടര ലിഖ ടധിരഭ്യധ്ഡ?
Simba, it's to die for.
ന്ധ, ലാസ ടല്വബാാദ ലന ടടബുയ.
Shut up.
ഉണി.
I can't help it. I'm so hungry. I got to have a wildebeest.
മയ 151 ടഹൃല്യ. രാലവ്ധില്ാല. മയ നമ൦ണലിത്ഥ ടല ബട ഡ്ധാ.
Stay put.
ഉധഠ്ധിറിടണ-ഠിദണന.
Can't I just pick off one of the little sick ones?
ദിവാലി ടര വിയ്യാ ടലല്ധ൭ന ഭി?
No. We wait for the signal from Scar.
1൦16. ഗ൭ ഡഘാധഖഖയ ഠ്ം്വാഠ്ട ടല.
There he is. Let's go.
൮ ഠി. ഷുവി൨.
"Little roar."
വ്പറുദ്ധന്ന ഭം."
Look, sire, the herd is on the move.
1൦0 ഡാബ്വ, യാന സ ട്ടേ
-Odd. -Mufasa, quick.
-൧0ല൨. പിഗിധ്ടടമ, ല്യട.
Stampede in the gorge.
ലസ്വധമഥ സസ 11൧00.
-Simba's down there! -Simba?
-ടമ്പാട ഠ9 ഠി ടിയ! മമ്പാട്‌?
Zazu, help me!
ക്മമ്ധ, 10 ടര!
Your father is on the way! Hold on!
ഷുരിഥാദ യ ടി ലാലുടിദ്്‌ ദ്വ
Hurry!
ല്രോദ്ധി
There! There on that tree!
൧ ടമ! 2 0൦൪!
Hold on, Simba!
ലല്റ വവ, ടമ്മ!
Dad!
തി!
Scar, this is awful!
ല്ല, ഡിസ ദ്ദ ബ്‌!
What'll we do? What'll we do?
൧്വാ ലാന്ഡ്‌
I'll go back for help, that's what I'll do.
മയ മിത 0ല സ്ന്ദവാസ്ധമല, ധ൮൭ന൭ ടര മിത ാധല.
Dad!
തി!
Scar!
ദ്‌
-Brother. -Brother, help me!
4൧൭൭. -൧ഠ॥ 0൦ ടത
Long live the king.
ഉദ്ധ ഡബ്വ.
No!
ഠി
Dad!
തി!
Dad?
ഷുഖ്്ന
Dad, come on.
൧൮൭൨, ന്ഥി.
You got to get up.
ല്രോഖ്ധില്പാനാഥന.
Dad?
ഷുഖ്്ന
We got to go home.
9 ഹല്ഖ ാധിടനാ ഭ ബന.
Help!
101൦!
Somebody!
ടലടില്വാ ല്‍
Anybody.
ടലടില്വാട ടദ്യമില.
Help.
101൦൩.
Simba. What have you done?
സ്സ. ൧൮൭ മഴമിഠ്ല്വാധല്?
There were wildebeests, and he tried to save me.
൧ഠ9 ലാബി, ൦ ൮൭൨ ലോ ടടിണമിത്ഥ ടര.
It was an accident. I didn't mean for it to happen.
9 ടന്ന. മയ 151 ടാ൭ ൭ ലിഖ്ബ്ാലില്വ.
Of course. Of course you didn't.
ഠി ല്ധ. ധാ സ്വ ്ചം
No one ever means for these things to happen.
11909 ടില്യാട മിത്ഥ ടാ ഗലിത്ഥ ടലാലാി ല്ര്ാലില്വ.
But the king is dead.
1111: 1-11-11
And if it weren't for you, he'd still be alive.
ദ്രിദ്ധവാധിയ് ദ്വ ഗ്ല, ിദ നട വോ ടത.
What will your mother think?
൧്വാ ൭90൮ യിനി?
What am I going to do?
൧്വാാമധടമുതാധമ്ന
Run away, Simba.
10 ടലി ടിവി, ട്ട.
Run. Run away and never return.
ലി. ൧ ഠ്കിട്ബ്‌ ബനാ ഭ്പാദ॥.
Kill him.
്ധന്ധ ഠി.
Whoa!
മവ
Hey, there he goes. There he goes.
റല, ഠി ഠ്൭൨൧0ലഠ. ൧19 9൩0൬.
So go get him.
പ്ഒഠി 0൦150 ത്വാ ഠ1ഒ.
There ain't no way I'm going in there.
പ്രാ ന്ലഭ്വാ ടര നമായ ഭ ട൭.
What, you want me to come out looking like you, cactus butt?
൧്വാഠ, യിലി ടമുര 1909 നടന യപാധസ്ധഥിത്ഡട?
But we got to finish the job.
ലവ ന ലാല്ധ ടലിടടലിത്ഥ ടട ല്‍.
Well, he's as good as dead out there anyway.
8:11 116] 1൭10൨0 ടലദണ൭ ഠവല ടന൭.
And if he comes back, we'll kill him.
ദ്രിട്ധ 919 'ഭമ്പാ॥॥, 9 വാധന്ധ്വ്ല ഠ1ഒ.
Yeah! You hear that?
ച്‌ ഹാല ഘ്ന
If you ever come back, we'll kill you!
ദ്രിട്ധ ഴ്ല്റിഭവമ്പാ! ൫ ടവ, യി മിരഡാധസ്ധി മിറ
Mufasa's death is a terrible tragedy.
നബായ്്ര്‍്ധ്ദട ദ ടദ്ധ നമഠ൦ഠി.
But to lose Simba, who had barely begun to live...
ലവ ഭവി സാം, റബ ടല്യ നന്ധിലിത്ന ഭവാ...
For me, itis a deep, personal loss.
ദഖറ്റ ടയ, 9 ടദ്ധിശവ്വ്ന ൮ നബ്വത്ധിഘ.
So it is with a heavy heart that l assume the throne.
പ്ഒഠി നന്മ! ട്ര നല്ലി ചന്ന ബ്‌.
Yet out of the ashes of this tragedy we shall rise
പ്ന്ധന ഠി ടലാലി॥ഗന്നമ്ാാഠം।ബ ന ത്ഥ യാന ടന്ധിട
to greet the dawning of a new era
ധന്ധിഗനനസമ്പാഥിക്ലാട ജെ ഠാബ
in which lion and hyena come together
ഠി നന്ദ ടന 0 ഠധോധ്ഥലടഡ നമി
in a great and glorious future.
ഠി ടലാധല നട ലാ ൭ 015 ൦1൭൭.
Get out! Get out! Get out of here!
ലലെ! ലല! ലല 0 ടബ്‌!
I love this! Bowling for buzzards.
മയ ധ്യ! ഴിസഘന്ധവാധസനാ യ.
Gets 'em every time.
ഴിലഘര ത്ഥ ലശന്മ ടലില്വ ൪.
Hey, Timon, you better come look.
ലല, ന, ലാവാലിമമ്വംല്‍.
I think it's still alive.
മൃ ടടാ।ടനടടി ബ്ലോ.
All righty, what have we got here?
ഒലി, ല്യാ്ന!ന്൯ ഠ്ദ്വ്ധ്വാ ബി?
Jeez, it's a lion! Run, Pumbaa, move it!
ചിണന്, ടിനാദ ഡാസ്‌! 1, ല്വമ്പാടദ, ലോബ്‌
Hey, Timon, it's just a little lion.
ലല, ന, ഒ ബന ടന 1൪൭൦1.
Look at him. He's so cute and all alone.
1൦100 ഠി. ലാലി ഗനേല്‍ ഠ്ബാലടനാ।്ദ.
-Can we keep him? -Pumbaa, are you nuts?
-8ഠ1ല൩ ന നസ്സ്‌? ്വമ്സാമ, യ്ലിറ്്റില്യ്ന?
You're talking about a lion. Lions eat guys like us.
൧ഡമിവാലഥലിത്വാ ന്മ ടന. ൭൧3 നമി്ഖിഘഗ ടലാന്‌ ൩൭.
-But he's so little. -He's going to get bigger.
-ല്വാി ഠി ലാല ൪൦1. ൧19 മ൭൫ ടനണമിന്൩ഥാടടല.
Maybe he'll be on our side.
ഗ്ധ്ിന്൩ ഠിദ ത്ഥ നസ്ുഘാലല്‍ട്വ റ.
That's the stupidest thing l ever heard. Maybe he'll...
ധിട്ന്ാലത്ഥ ദിന ൦9൦൩ 0൭൦൬൭ ടര നഹോല. 'ള്‍്ഥ1ന്൩ ഠദ...
Hey, I've got it. What if he's on our side?
ലല, ട്ര 91 ഠ്വ. റ്റല്നമനമ രിദ്ധ ഠി നസുഘാലട്വ ന്മ?
You know, having a lion around might not be such a bad idea.
ദലിത ഠി ട്നാദ ന്ധ്യിന്ന ടഡ്ടോടി
So we're keeping him?
പഠി 119 001൦൩ നസ്ുന്ധാ്സുത?
Of course. Who's the brains of this outfit?
ഠി ല്ധ. കല്യാ 01൮ ബ്മന്മ്‌?
My point exactly.
ധി നലത്ധഠ ടര.
Jeez, I'm fried. Let's get out of here and find some shade.
ഠ്വ, നമു. [ഗി 09 ലാ നലല 1൭1൨.
-You okay, kid? -l guess so.
ഡമി ല്വാ-ഖ്വാദ, 1൪ ്റമിസ്ാലവ്ധിട.
You nearly died.
൧ഡഘില്മന്പാ! നല്‍ ൭൦.
I saved you.
മയ ലല നബഭിണമിത്ഥ മലി
Well, Pumbaa helped. A little.
ല്വന്സാമലാധ0 നലമ്പാമ്ധ. ൭൦1൩.
Thanks for your help.
ലണ യ൭ടിന മട ലവസ്ധന മലം
Hey, where you going?
ലി, ദില നമ ഡ്‌?
Nowhere.
1ദിലിഭ നമനമ-ന൭൫൭.
Gee, he looks blue.
൧9 നന്ധദ്ധാാധ ഥന.
-I'd say brownish gold. -No, no, no. 1 mean he's depressed.
ടമ മട ഡനമസ്ര ലേ ട്വ. ലിയ, ാധിയ. ൧൭ നന്വാട൦൦10൩.
Kid, what's eating you?
൧ മഗ്യിനനല്യ് ബിഷ?
Nothing. He's at the top of the food chain.
ലിബി ദ നലിത്ഥ അ. ദല ഠിദ ലട ടന ണ്ല്ഠന ന്ത.
The food chain!
ംസ്ലി്റ നിത്‌
So, where you from?
ട്ഒഠി, ടഴലിഥ്ലി നമ?
Who cares? I can't go back.
ലെഠ്ധി। ല്ാട? മദര 1൦൦൩ ലധി0൭.
You're an outcast. That's great. So are we.
൧ഡിവലല ട്ട. മറ്റടമ൨യ്ബി ാധ്്ാല്ധ.
-What'd you do, kid? -Something terrible.
൮൭ ടലി ലം ന -ടടട്ധദ്ധ വന ബിം
-But I don't want to talk about it. -We don't want to hear about it.
ല്യി ടര പനല്ഡ 0ലേ്ഖ്സര. രാധ ലഗന്ല്ഡ ന്നോ.
Come on, Timon. Anything we can do?
101൦1൭1൨, നന൦൩. 8ംല്വ്യബി സ്വ?
Not unless you can change the past.
1ഠ്ടനല്ല്ബിത്ഥ ഡേയില്‍ നനാധാല നട ടിന.
You know, kid, in times like this, my buddy Timon here says,
൧॥ല്വാടാദ ഡലിവഡ ടലാലാ്ി, യധാഥ ടര 71നം0 ടട്ല്ധാലിയ്ട,
"You got to put your behind in your past."
"ലിഷ ന്മ ടല ംിച്ി.”
No, no, no.
8ധിത്വ,ാധിയ്ന,ാധിയ്ന.
-[ mean... -Amateur.
ഗീടിദ്ധാ ടര... ന്ഥ.
Lie down before you hurt yourself.
ലല ല്വാലാ്ന ടലാല്ധന മഴമിഥടഠ്ലമിത്ഥ ഠി ലിം
It's, "You got to put your past behind you."
ഷരസ, "വടം നനാ ലിഖ ല്ധ.”
Look, kid, bad things happen, and you can't do anything about it, right?
ല്റ്ബി, ടടടധദ്ധവതനാ ൧ഥഡിവാല്ലിവ, ൦൩൭ 1ധാംല്വാധമല്വാ-ല്വാ, 07
-Right. -Wrong!
-8ദ്ധി. ദിവ്‌
When the world turns its back on you,
്യാദ്ധിട ദ്ധി മലാന,
you turn your back on the world.
൯19 ലാല്ധി॥ത്ഥ ട്വ ്ധബ്ട ബി.
Well, that's not what I was taught.
ധവാധിത്ന മഥ ടര ഠ1ഠ101॥൦
Then maybe you need a new lesson.
ഗ്ല ന്൩ യലാലിധിത്ഥ ഠിഠിത്ാബ.
Repeat after me.
വി! തത ടര.
-Hakuna matata. -What?
-ലഒഡഗട 7൭4൭൭. വാമ?
Hakuna matata.
൧൭:൧ഥട 7൭൭൭.
It means "no worries".
ഴിലിദ്ധഗ്ുയ, "19 നടി."
What a wonderful phrase.
(മയി ൮൭൩൭ ലാട.
Hakuna matata.
൧൭:൧ഥട 7൭൭൭.
Ain't no passing craze
7ഒഗഥ 74൭൧ റ്റെറ്റുടറ ലൊ!
It means no worries
70ഒ൧5൧൮0)൭ 4ഒ9ഠ്ട 79ടഒ4ഒ0
For the rest of your days
ക്ലാദ൦(ഒഥററ 70റ്ഥാ ഗ്ഒ
It's our problem-free philosophy
൧൧൭൧ 7൭5൭7൭7 4ഒഥ൧ഒ 70൭൭5൭൭
Hakuna matata
൧൭:൧ഥട നദ
Hakuna matata?
൧൭:൧ഥട സന?
-Yeah. It's our motto. -What's a motto?
൭. ധി നം ൭൬. ഗീഠഠ 1൨ ലാമ?
Nothin’. What's-a-motto with you?
11909 ഖ്വാ3. വാട നടടടിലറ മലി
You know, kid, these two words will solve all your problems.
൧॥ ്ര ലാലിയ ബി ത്ഥ ടിടി ടലന്ധദ നടി യല
That's right. Take Pumbaa, for example. Why...
ഒപ്ധി സ. ഠംണ്ംസ്൭, ധാമ.
When he was a young warthog
(൫൧൪ ന്‌ഒ ന൭57 79
When I was a young warthog
(൫൧൪ ൭:൧ നഒട൧ സലഠ്൭
-Very nice. -Thanks.
ലാട ടര. ലന ൭510.
He found his aroma lacked a certain appeal
൧49 ടലറ്ല ൧൭ഥ)൭ ൭൩൭! (ഒന ഘൃക്ഥകററ്വക്ഥ
He could clear the savanna after every meal
ക്ലല്ാദടട വട ഗന ഖഷ്ഗ ടല ഒ൪൭൧ഥ !ഒ7്‌ ല്ലാ
I'ma sensitive soul
൧ധഥല്നഒ ട്‌
Though I seem thick-skinned
14ഒ(൭൧൧൧ ഗ7൭൩൧0൭ഥലന്നഥ്ഭ 4ഥെദ്‌
And it hurt that my friends never stood downwind
7(൫വ൮൭ ഗദഥഡ ൧7൭ ൭ക്ഥ-ഒ൭ര്ഥ 2091-2൧൧൭! (ഒല൭ഥ൭
-And, oh, the shame -He was ashamed
-2ഒഥ, 0, ൧ല൭ഠാ൭ 7൭൧)൭ -8ല്ഒ്രാട 70൭൧)൭ ന്ഒ
-Thought of changing my name -Oh, what's in a name?
൧൧൧൮0൭ ൧൭൦ സന ഥ്ക7 ഗടനട -07, ഒറ്ദ ഒഠാ൭ 0൭ഠ്9 നട?
And I got downhearted
എഡ ഥാഥ ഥാലഡ്ഥഭ (ഒ൭
-How did you feel? -Every time that...
-൧൧൭:൫൭൧ ൧ലഒട3ഗനനഥ? കഥ (ക൧ ഒ...
-Hey, not in front of the kids. -Oh, sorry.
ലാബി ഠി ലോ ധാല്റാധഠ്ട ൨0൨. ഴി.
Hakuna matata
൧൭:൧ഥട നദ
What a wonderful phrase
൭൭-൪൭ ൭൧ ഗെ!
Ain't no passing craze
7ഒഗഥ 74൭൧ റ്റെറ്റുടറ ലൊ!
It means no worries
70ഒ൧5൧൮0)൭ 4ഒ9ഠ്ട 79ടഒ4ഒ0
For the rest of your days
ക്ലാദ൦(ഒഥററ 70റ്ഥാ ഗ്ഒ
Yeah, sing it, kid.
വ, സസ്ധിത്ഥ, 91൦.
It's our problem-free
൧൧൭൧ 7൭5൭7ഒ
Philosophy
7 ഒഗ്൧ഒ ൩൭൭5൭4൭
Hakuna matata
൧൭:൧ഥട നദ
Welcome to our humble home.
ലന റ്റ ലമ്ല്വാഥ്യില്ത.
-You live here? -We live wherever we want.
ഗി്വ്ഘാട! 9 ടബ്‌? രി ഘാ! ഠി നടന്മ-നമന്മ ട്വ.
Yep. Home is where your rump rests.
ദപ്ധി. ൧ നന യഖബിാല൭02 ിട്്ധിംഡണദ്സിതബ.
It's beautiful.
0ഠ്മന്൭.
I'm starved.
[ല്വാ്ൂ൭.
I'm so hungry I could eat a whole zebra.
മതില്‌ വന്ാല്ത്ന 0ഠ1ല൩ നദ്ത്ഥ ടടല്‍രല വാദ വാല്‍.
We're fresh out of zebra.
ദ്വി ഠ്ദ്വിഷ്ല്്ടവഠ്ട ലല.
Any antelope?
൧ഠ9 ന്ലില്വാ?
-Hippo? -Nope.
ഠി? 1909.
Listen, kid, if you live with us, you have to eat like us.
ദരിദ്ധ നല! ലട തി, ഡേോ്ലകമ നിത ടലാല്‌ (യബി.
Hey, this looks like a good spot to rustle up some grub.
ലി, ന്ഥ 1ബ ന്വാ ടട! ന്ധി നമി.
What's that?
്വാ ദ്ധ?
A grub. What's it look like?
വട. ല്യാി?
Gross.
൩൭.
Tastes like chicken.
ടാ സുയ ടലാപസി രന.
Slimy yet satisfying.
ലില്ലി നന്ധടടിത്ല.
These are rare delicacies.
വി നലി്ത്നാനര്ലുലനാ ഠരന്ധി.
Piquant, with a very pleasant crunch.
ഴിലാട്ിറക്ല, ോബിഭാന്നാസര് ന്ലം
You'll learn to love them.
൧ഡഘിലാടടി മിത്൩ാട്ല്യല നനസ്ുവധിവ്സുര.
I'm telling you, kid, this is the great life,
ലെവല്‌, ഠിം ൩ ഭ്വഠ്ധ്ോബത്നാ ലനാ,
no rules, no responsibilities.
119 ലാലഡമ, 0ദഠ്9 റ്റാഥ്്്്യ്ലോ.
The little cream-filled kind.
പ്ലബ്ട വയനാ നനാുഥ്ഥഘ! ന്ന.
And best of all, no worries.
വനാ ന സ്വ, വദ നടി.
Well, kid?
ച്ദഠി, ഠി
Oh, well. Hakuna matata.
80൭൩. ഥഒഗ്ഥദ ന൭൭൭.
Slimy, yet satisfying.
ലില്ലി നന്ധടടിത്ല.
That's it.
ധി ഠി.
Hakuna matata
൧൭:൧ഥട നദ
-Hakuna... -lt means no worries
191൮0൭... പിഒ) 4ഒഠ്ട നട9ടഒഒ7
For the rest of your days
ക്ലാദ൦(ഒഥററ 70റ്ഥാ ഗ്ഒ
It's our problem-free
൧൧൭൧ 7൭5൭7ഒ
Philosophy
7 ഒഗ്൧ഒ ൩൭൭5൭4൭
Hakuna matata
൧൭:൧ഥട നദ
Yeah
[ക]
Ta-ta!
1-9
Nobody knows
74ഒറ്9 .54900൭ 49൧0൧
The trouble I've seen
൭൮൧ ഖഗ
My sorrow
(൫ടധ്ഗേഥധ
Zazu, do lighten up.
൧92൨, ലോല ടി.
Sing something with a little bounce in it.
പമസ്ധിത്ബിട്വിാഥത്ന ലാ! മലം
It's a small world after all
൧ാഗ്ഒ ൨7 ലോലനദെറ്റ)ട ;ഒല7്‌
No, no! Anything but that!
1൭ സാലിറ കാലാ 00 ടട്ച്സ്ധ!
I've got a lovely bunch of coconuts
൧൮ ഒറ്ദ ലേഗസഥഥ (൭ഒ൧൭ )൭൧ഥറ ദേറ്മ്ഥ
Deedle dee dee
൧7൨൭ റെ റെ
There they are a-standing in a row
ക്ലു 4ലഥേഥ ടമാണ്‌
Big ones, small ones, some as big as your head
൭൧൮ 2ടെഒഷഥറ്റ ൭, ഒറ്9 )9൭൧ “ലാട (ക്ാട'ഒ
I would never have had to do this with Mufasa.
മര 1ടില്ാല്ധ ൭ ടന്ധട ബി ടലി ്ര്‍്ഥ്ദടദ നട വോ.
What? What did you say?
൧്യാമ? ല്യാഠ ്ലിലിത്മ?
-Nothing. -You know the law.
11909 മാദ-്0. ഡമിവല്ഡ ല്ഡമ്സുമ.
Never, ever mention that name in my presence. I am the king!
പാ ടയ നനബഘാധ നന യ ഠി ഠില്ാന ടര. മയ്യ!
Yes, sire, you are the king.
൭, ധബിവ, യില ഭ്്മ.
I... Lonly mentioned it to illustrate the differences
മയ ടര ഉന നന൭ിത്ഥ ലാനാ
in your royal managerial approaches.
നല ലേ ലാനലിന്മ്ന മ്മില്‍.
-Hey, boss. -What is it this time?
ലി, 05. ൮൭ ൧൨19 യ ബി?
-We got a bone to pick with you. -I'll handle this.
(നമ ണല്മഠ്ധ ശ്വാ മ്മി ജല ട്ര ധഡടിത്ന.
Scar, there's no food, no water.
ലേവ, നല്യ്ഥമഥ 90 ൭ ല്വ്ഘട.
Yeah. It's dinner time and we ain't got no stinking entrées.
൭. ഥം ലാം ഡമ്ഡ നല്ത്ഥനട്ണ ൦൩൩൭ നടടിവാല്ധന ദ്ല്ാ ന്ത.
It's the lionesses' job to do the hunting.
ഴില്ധധബ ലട ടന ൧൮02.
Yeah, but they won't go hunt.
വം ്ല്വാി നല ഘാ ലാല! നനസ്പാധബ.
-Eat Zazu. -You wouldn't want me.
ച്ഗ്ടിരബില ൧൭൭൮. ഡിവി നല്നലിത്ഥ ടര.
I'd be so tough and gamey and...
ഉന ടര ൭ ഠ്ദബാനാദ്ധ ലബിട...
Zazu, don't be ridiculous. All you need is a little garlic.
മമ്ധ, നാന നല്ുഡില്പഗ്ടം മസ ഗലധ സ്വാ ട൦ഠിസ്വായന 0൧൨.
I thought things were bad under Mufasa.
നമിത മാന്ടെ ലാ ലഡിലശ്മ മ്പ.
-What did you say? -l said Muf...
യാ മഴമിലിത്മ? ദര തിയ്‌...
lsaid qué pasa?
മുര ിത്മ, 0൧ 0൭൭7
Good. Now get out.
ദദറ്റ്ട. ടലി ഭ്ധല ഠി ടബ്‌.
But we're still hungry.
ല്വ। യി നടടിവില്വാ.
Out!
ദ്ധ!
-Whoa! Nice one, Simba. -Thanks.
ഗവ ധാതാ ടമ്മ. ലന ൭510.
-Man, I'm stuffed. -Me, too.
79000, ബസ. ടയ ാധന ടണമ.
l ate like a pig.
മയ നദ്ിത്ഥ നഹാദ്ട്വ്ത്ാലാ!.
Pumbaa, you are a pig.
ല്വന്ധാ, നനന ഒഴമിസ്ധാലാ!.
Right.
ല്ലി.
-Timon? -Yeah?
നന?
Ever wonder what those sparkling dots are up there?
ല്ലാ സട ദ്വാമിര്വാസിപാസ്ധ്ഥലിറിദ്ധ 9 ദടടധ?
Pumbaa, I don't wonder, I know.
ല്വന്ധാാ, ടര പവനു ബസ, ട്ര നന്മ ദ്ധ.
What are they?
വാടിയ?
They're fireflies.
വധ 50൪0-൪0.
Fireflies that got stuck up in that big blueish-black thing.
10-ഭ്ഗ്ഥ ലില്‍യ്‌ ട്ടാ ടല ഡനമാസിക്സ്ലനടന
Gee.
ചിന
l always thought they were balls of gas
ലന ബി ടര നുമിത്ിട ൧ലാം1ഒ റുടട
burning billions of miles away.
ന ടോ 'നല്ത്വ ലാംബ ലി ടബ്‌.
Pumbaa, with you, everything's gas.
ല്വമ്ധാമ, ൧9] ലിം ടല്ധസ്ര ലാല.
Simba, what do you think?
ന്നാ, വാ ൧ലഠ്ല്വാ ലിറ
Well, don't know.
5ന്മവി50൩.
Come on. Give, give, give, give.
൧൮0. ഠലിത്വാ0, ല്ഷ്വാിട.
Come on. We told you ours. Please?
1011൭൨. വ്്ി ദ്ല്വാല്! ല്ലാ. 8ംല്വിമ്ന
Well...
ഒലി...
Somebody once told me
പം 11
that the great kings of the past are up there watching over us.
ലയ ല്യം ലാമ ടിന നനലിയലിത്ിന്ട ഠ്‌ മട ടമ.
Really?
വല്യ?
You mean a bunch of royal dead guys are watching us?
[ഗിലിദ്ധാ യി ടോലയ്ധാ।ന യന 9൭1 ണന ടാ നനലന്തിത്ലിന്മ?
-Who told you something like that? -Yeah, yeah.
ല്യം ടന്ധദഡ? 1 -11:11-11:11:
-What mook made that up? -Yeah. Pretty dumb, huh?
ദ്ധി നന്മ ല്‍൭ ട്വ യ? ൭. 8ംഠ്ഠ്വ്മ, യന
-You're killing me. -Yeah.
-൧ലഠമ്വാല്ധ്‌ ടര. 9.
Was it something I said?
മയ ്ലടില്വാ ദയ്വിയ്ന?
Simba?
ടന്ധാമ?
He's... He's alive? He's alive!
൧൭... ഗദ നട വോ? ഉട നടടി ബ്ലോ!
It is time.
ഉലാ നടു.
A-wimoweh, a-wimoweh
൧-40ല൨, 9-07707ല?
In the jungle, the mighty jungle
൧൭ഒന ഗഥ്൦െ, ഗഥ്൦ )ഒഥറ 4“ലാഒ!
The lion sleeps tonight
കറ9 ട്ഒററ്റ 7റ്ഥ്‌
The lion sleeps to...
കഥറു9 ട്ഒററ്റ 7...
Il can't hear you, buddy. Back me up.
മുര 1മഠ്നഹോല്‌ ടവ മി്പത്ധ. 0൩0 ടര.
A-Pumbaa-bum-baa-weh
൧-൧൧൩൧൭9-൧൧൧-൧൭9-ഥ൭൦൨
Pumbaa? Pumbaa?
ല്വന്ധാ? ല്വമ്പാദദ്‌?
Timon?
11ന൦ന?
Pumbaa?
ല്വന്പാമമ?
Pumbaa! Pumbaa!
ല്വന്ധാ! ല്ധസ്ാദട!
Pumbaa, Pumbaa! Hey, what's going on?
ല്രന്പാടട, ല്വമ്പാമ! റല, ല്വാട ടഠഠ് ലലില്വ ബി?
She's going to eat me!
൧9 മത നലന്പാല്നന ട്ര!
Whoa! Jeez, why do I always have to save your...
൯! മഠ്ധിഘി, ജ്വാല ടര ടബിദടദ ലാമ ടലണമിത്ഥ...
Don't worry, buddy. I'm here for you. Everything's going to be okay.
പാന റ്ടാധ, രല. കേര്ാലടാണട ഡോ മരന്ധബ്ുയ മിത്ഥ ടല.
Get her! Bite her head!
ലു)ല്ത്ഥ ദ! വിരാലി!
Go for the jugular! The jugular!
ലാ ൭ നലസ്മ! വരനന
See, I told you he'd come in handy.
ല്ഠൃലപത്ഥ ടര ഠ്ദ്വ്യ്ദ ഭ്ലിദ ഡ ധാല്ധന്മ്വ്ധാ3.
Nala?
1:10
Is it really you?
൧ഡഘിറമ്ന്ധ?
-Who are you? -It's me. Simba.
മല്യ യിലി? ബി ടമ. ടാ.
Simba?
ടന്ധാമ?
Whoa! How did you...
7൩ ഒംാച്നടന്മ യം...
-Wow! -Where did you come from?
ഗ7ഠഡ! ഗമി്ട്മനാ ഠ്നമന്മ?
This is gr... It's great to see you!
ലാസ... ബ്വേ ബര ല)ധന്ധാട ലു മഴമറ
-Hey, what's goin’ on here? -What are you doing here?
ലി, ല്യാന് ട൦ഠ്ണോാ ാലില്വ ബല്‍? യായാ യ്ല്വാധട്ഠി ട്‌?
What am I doing here? What are you doing here?
൧്വാട ടദ്യരാധ്ഠി ടല? യാന യല ഠി ടബ്‌?
Hey! What's goin’ on here?
ലല! ക്യു ടട ലലില്വ ബ്‌?
Timon, this is Nala. She's my best friend.
11ന൦൩, ബട. ൧9 മഗാ ദര.
-Friend? -Yeah. Hey, Pumbaa, come over here.
രഗ? ൭. 11%, ല്വമ്പാഠ, നട ടബ്‌.
Nala, this is Pumbaa. Pumbaa, Nala.
പിട, ബ്‌ ലവ്പാടട. ല്വമ്പാഠെ, [ഒ1മ.
-Pleased to make your acquaintance. -The pleasure is all mine.
-ദലമ്പാനമ ലുധന്വാട ലു മ്മി ദണട-ടണട്ല്വന്മ.
How do you... Whoa, whoa! Time out! Let me get this straight.
൧്വാട നല്ല... ൪൩, ൩! ച ടര ചല്ിത്നാദ്ധി-ാട്ധി
You know her, she knows you.
ഗലി 9, ദ 03 ഗലി
But she wants to eat him, and everybody's okay with this?
വല്യ 01 നല്ഡ നലിത്ഥ ഥ്ധസ്സാമട, 0 ട്വ ഘു ഖ്ാടംാഥ്‌?
-Did I miss something? -Relax, Timon.
ടമ 9 ലയില്‍ ല്വാമ-ല്വാമിവ്ന? ലമ, നണ൦൩.
Wait till everyone finds out you've been here all this time.
1൦10൭0 ൯൬൯ ല്ാഖ്ധിട ടസ്ഡധട മല 1ലിഡ ദഴമിഠ്ട ഠി ടബ്‌ ടല ബ്‌.
And your mother, what will she think?
1 യല, ലാട ലട ന്‌?
She doesn't have to know. Nobody has to know.
8-111-11: 11909 ടില്വാാധനവാല്ധ ലഡ.
Of course they do. Everyone thinks you're dead.
[ഴിലട്ലിദ്സ്വാലിധ. ലന്ധട നാ ന യറി നല്‍.
They do?
വല്യ?
Yeah. Scar told us about the stampede.
൭. ലേ 9 ല്മ്ഡ സ്നോ ന്വാധ്ന൦൩ബ.
He did? What else did he tell you?
വല്യ ല്യാിാവന ഠ3 ന്ല്ഡ?
What else matters? You're alive. And that means, you're the king.
1ദിവാസ്നാ ന കഴമ നടി ബ്ലോ. വ്ലിന്മസര, യില ഭ്വ്മ.
King? Lady, have you got your lions crossed!
മല്യ? ലന, ഡേിറാല്വാധണകടില്ാാടെട്!
King?
മല്യ?
Your Majesty, I gravel at your feet.
ദധബിവ, ടര നബ്ഭമ്പാധറ വറ മലം
-Stop it. -It's not gravel, it's grovel.
-ലസ്ിത്ഥ. ലിയ നസ്ൂന്പാധ, നബ്ഭമ്പാമ.
And don't! He's not the king. Are you?
സ്ത്‌ ഥി ാധിത്ഥ ല്യം. ധന
-No. -Simba!
ലിയ. -ടമ്പാട!
No, I'm not the king. Maybe I was gonna be,
150 ടര ാധിത്ഥ ദ്യ. ഗ്ധിന്വാന്ല ടധബ്ബ നടാ ദ്ധ,
but that was a long time ago.
1111 1:111:111:1 1:11
Let me get this straight. You're the king? And never told us?
ദല ടര ചല്ിത്നാദ്ധി-ാട്ി. കഴമ ദ? ൧൨ ധവല്ലാന്മ്ഡിയ്‌?
-Look, I'm still the same guy. -But with power.
ദ്യ നട രനാ ടട. ല്യിവന നബി॥॥റിവടടട.
Could you guys excuse us for a few minutes?
8ഠ1ല ഴ്ലിവാല്ധമ 1ാടിത്ിതബി ടന്ന ലാന?
Hey, whatever she has to say,
ലിലി, ഖ്വായ്ദ നാസിത്ല്ത്ഥ,
she can say in front of us, right, Simba?
ിാഠില്‍്വിയ്ലിത്ഥ ലാരി, ലാബ്ബി ചം, ടമ്പാട?
Maybe you'd better go.
ടാ സുമിലാസാലി മ്മി.
It starts. You think you know a guy.
9 ഠദ്വാന്ധിദ. നാഖിത്ബിന്ദ ട്വാവലലാന്മലെ ൩൭ ടട.
Timon and Pumbaa, you learn to love 'em.
11ന൦0 00 ഥ്വമ്പാട, പമ്പാടി ഡേ്ലാദട ടിയ നലല്‍൭.
What?
വാമ?
What is it?
(ദറല്വാ ബി?
It's like you're back from the dead.
ടാ ട൦0150-൦ി ഡേ ബിഠ്വോ സ്സ.
You don't know how much this will mean to everyone.
൧ഡഘിറവല്വല്ഡാങലൊട ല്നമിന്മസര വാ! ടന്ധദ ൦൭0.
What it means to me.
8ല്ല്യാധാലന്നമിനസുമ ഒ മറ! ടയ.
-Hey, it's okay. -I've really missed you.
ലി, 1910 ലാമ. ദ്യ ണമ നലനര്‍്ധി ലിം
I've missed you, too.
മുതാഥ നലല യം
I tell you, Pumbaa. This stinks.
മയ ദിഷ്വാ ടലഷ്ഥമ്, ല്വ്പാദമ. പ്ലാ.
Sorry.
ഗി.
Not you! Them!
8ധിധ്ഥ യി 'ഴിലല൪!
Him, her, alone.
ടല, ടി 999, ലിമി.
What's wrong with that?
൧്യാ ടിയ?
-l can see what's happening -What?
41൭൧൧ ൭ ദ൧ഥ 4൭൨7 വാമ?
-And they don't have a clue -Who?
ഒ നലല (ഒഥറ൦ഥേററ 'ഒ്൭0൧ -ടല്യാമ?
They'll fall in love and here's the bottom line
ലല ൭൧൭ ഥഗ ഗഡ റ ൧൨൧൭൧ (൭ സ്ഥാഥഥക
Our trio's down to two
൭൧ ൧ ഥ90ഒ റ്ഥ൭
The sweet caress of twilight
൧൧ല൭ ൧ഒഡ 5൦൭൭൭
There's magic everywhere
7(൫൭(൭൧൧ഒ൭൧ഥ ൨ നഥട-7ന ഗദ
And with all this romantic atmosphere
൧75ലഥാഥഥറ 59 ഒറദ നട ൨
Disaster's in the air
ഗ്ട ഒ്ഥ വ്‌ 2൭4൭
Can you feel the love tonight?
280൨൭ (ഥാ ഖഷ്ഗ ഒ നട(ഒന ൨7
The peace the evening brings
൫(ഒറടറ്റ ൭൧ റ്ദ1ഒററ്റ 2ലടഒനട 7൭4൭7
The world for once
ഗാഗ ഒശ്ഗസൃട
In perfect harmony
൧൭ഒ 4ലാടഗസ്നഠലഒെ ടലന്വാഗഥ്നദ
With all its living things
8ലടഒനട ടെ (കവവ്ഥെ
So many things to tell her
2ലറ്ഡ്ഥ ഥലുടഗഥറ്ഗ ;ഗര്ഭക്ഥ
But how to make her see
7ഒഥ൧ ൧ടറ്റടനഥട 2ഠ0൭൨ (ധലഒ൭൪൭൧
The truth about my past?
൧൭ഗ൪൭ ടെ ഒനഥ?
Impossible, she'd turn away from me
0൧5൭൧൧ ന്‌ ഒ(ഷഥ ൧ലഒ൧ ഖ്യു
He's holding back, he's hiding
൧9 ൧ല൭.54൭, 7൦൧൮)ലനാഥ്ൃസക്ഥ ടഒടഥഥ
But what, I can't decide
൧൧൭൭൧ ൭, (൧ ൭ല്ഗെഥ
Why won't he be the king I know he is?
(ഒഥട്യാട ന്‌ഒ ലറ്ററഥ 7൮൭൨ 7൭ ൮)൭ഥറ൮ (൧ കഥ?
The king l see inside?
൧൭൭ ൬൭൧ ഒറ്9 റ്൭'ഒന ൨7൦)൭ ലറ്റ്‌?
Can you feel the love tonight?
280൨൭ (ഥാ ഖഷ്ഗ ഒ നട(ഒന ൨7
The peace the evening brings
൫(ഒറടറ്റ ൭൧ റ്ദ1ഒററ്റ 2ലടഒനട 7൭4൭7
The world for once
ഗാഗ ഒശ്ഗസൃട
In perfect harmony
൧൭ഒ 4ലാടഗസ്നഠലഒെ ടലന്വാഗഥ്നദ
With all its living things
8ലടഒനട ടെ (കവവ്ഥെ
Can you feel the love tonight?
280൨൭ (ഥാ ഖഷ്ഗ ഒ നട(ഒന ൨7
You needn't look too far
7ഒഥല്ഥാലസ്്‌ ൭൧
Stealing through
ലഗാ സന ഒടഥ
The night's uncertainties
ഒന ൭൧ ൧ഥഥ (കറ
Love is where they are
ഗഗ നലനദെറ്റ ഒറ്ദ വ്‌ (ലന്ഥാഗഒ
And if he falls in love tonight
ര൭ഥ ൨൭ ൭൧൧ വഗ സന ൧൧൨
It can be assumed
280൭ഒ7 വ൪൭ക്ഥ
His carefree days
ലാറ്ഥാറഷഗറ്റ ൧ഥലാടട
With us are history
28ലടഒനട (൭ണ ഒരഥ ഥലഖഗ്ഥ
In short, our pal
ടധ്വാഥഥവക, കഥ ൭
ls doomed
കഥ ൭5൧ ഒഗക്ഥ
Isn't this a great place?
ലാട ന്ധ ല്‍, ഖന?
It is beautiful.
1-111-11:
But I don't understand something.
വല്യ ടയ നട്ടി 1ിധ്ച്മന ന്ന ടടടധ്പ.
You've been alive all this time.
൧ഡലി൦ണടടി വോ ടട്ടണട ബ്‌.
Why didn't you come back to Pride Rock?
(ദറ്വാ യിലാ! ൭ ഒം ലി?
Well, I just needed to get out on my own, live my own life.
മയ ഡേനട ന്ധി ലാവാലഘാിത്വി, വിവോ യ്‌ ലേ ടം.
And I did, and it's great.
0൭൭ ടര ലല്വോടി, ൩19 ന ടല
We've really needed you at home.
൩ ണടവാലിധിത്ന മ്മി ടമ.
-No one needs me. -Yes, we do. You're the king.
119 ട്വ ാലിധിത്ന ടര. 1 ധാ്ല. ഷലി്ലത്ഥ നയതി.
Nala, we've been through this. I'm not the king. Scar is.
പി, 09 ഠ്വ ഥ്ര്ഘി ല്‍. 8ധിധ്ഥ ടര വ്യ, ഖ്വാ1 ടല്വേ.
Simba, he let the hyenas take over the Pride Lands.
ടന്വാട, ഠി ടല്വാ്ലിയ്ഥ ഠ്ധാധ! നലധടടച "0ല ഥി.
-What? -Everything's destroyed.
വാമ? ലട ലല സ്പടന്മ.
There's no food, no water.
ദ്വി ഠ്ദ്വിഷല്്ടന നടിത്ന്ന ഠ്0 ലി.
Simba, if you don't do something soon, everyone will starve.
ടന്വാട, രിദ മഗ്ല്റ്ല്ലാധ ടടടധദ്ധ, യി ടന്ധട മിരിഭ്ധാധ്ധന.
-l can't go back. -Why?
മദ്യ ഥി ല്ാധിടന. 1(൭ലല്വാമ?
-You wouldn't understand. -What?
ഡമിവലിറമ്ച്മണന. വാമ?
No, no, no. It doesn't matter. Hakuna matata.
1 ാല്പിഠ്ചം വ ണന. ൧൭:൧ഥട 7൭൭൭.
-What? -Hakuna matata.
വാമ? -ലഒഡഗട 7൭4൭൭.
It's something I learned out here. Sometimes bad things happen...
൮ ഖാനാ ടദരാല്ല്പ്ച ഠി ട്ബി. മഠ്ഘാതിദ ലാലി ാധ്സിവാലില്വ...
Simba...
ന്മ...
..and there's nothing you can do about it. So why worry?
൧൩൩൩൭ ൮0 ന്ധ വാമ ല്വാ-ല്വാമ. പഠി ന്യാ ിടദ്ധ സ്ഥാനത്‌?
-Because it's your responsibility. -Well, what about you? You left.
ലാലാ വ ഘനാ ഖലം ഡമി ല്ാധിട? ഡലിലാധന ഹല ഠ്‌ ടി.
I left to find help, and I found you.
മയാ നാലി ന്ധ, ഠി ട്ര 51 നന്ധി യം
Don't you understand? You're our only hope.
ഘ്ന ഡറി ടദ്ധ-ടഡസമ ല്വാിതി.
-Sorry. -What's happened to you?
ഗി. ൮൭ ൭൯൭ ഠോ യല്ല?
-You're not the Simba I remember. -You're right. I'm not.
ഡമിവാധിത്ഥ സസാ ഖര ഭന്മി!. -ഒല്ധി ഡ. ദര ഠ്ദ്വാഡിോട.
-Now are you satisfied? -No. Just disappointed.
വട 07 11951 ധന ഭഠദേഴമ.
You know, you're starting to sound like my father.
[1111-10-10] ടന ടയ ഠോ മുത ടര.
Good. At least one of us does.
ദമറ്റട1൭൨. ടടഡഘാ-വ്സമ ഠി വന ലറ്റ്‌.
You think you can just show up and tell me how to live my life?
൧ഡലി്ലനാമ യം ടാ ട്ബി ടലട്ധിയ 5 ൦൦ നാല ടര?
You don't even know what I've been through.
ലിലി പനമ്ഡ ട്രാ ടദുര ഠ്ദ്വ്ല്ധ.
l would if you'd just tell me.
1111111111:
-Forget it! -Fine!
1-111-11 ലിയ 0൭ യലിറിട്വ്‌
She's wrong. I can't go back.
ഗ്ന ടി. കര ദിവാംില്‍് ധ്യ.
What would it prove, anyway? It won't change anything.
൧്വാട റ്റ ധദ്ലാലാധ്ധ? 19 19100 നാഥാ ല്ാദ-്വാ.
You can't change the past.
ധം നലറ്ധാല് നട ടിന.
You said you'd always be there for me!
ഷുര്വ്യ്ദ ൧൭൨ ല്ത്ല ടബിദടദപാലടണട ട്ര!
But you're not.
1ല്വി വിമ
And it's because of me.
ല്ധബസു മന ട്ര.
It's my fault.
9 ടല ടര.
Come on, will you cut it out?
8ഠ1ല൩ 0൦ ലാന വമ ഥാല്്യ?
Can't cut it out. It'll grow right back!
1ലിവാംി്വാനന്ി. പൂം ടര ിവ്ഥ സ്ധിദ സ്വാ!
Creepy little monkey. Will you stop following me?
ഴിംസയനാ നന്മ്ഡിത്ഥ. 8ഠില൩ ലന ട്ര ട്ര?
-Who are you? -The question is, who are you?
മല്യ യിലി? ലട, ടില്വാമ മഴമറ
I thought I knew. Now I'm not so sure.
മയ ൭ ടര 0 ടര. ലയ്ഥാാ ടര 1മിവാലഘ്വാ മട.
Well, l know who you are. Come here. It's a secret.
മര 1ലി്ഡ ടില്വാാ മമ 1-11-11: 11011111
Enough! What is that supposed to mean?
ടവഠ്ട്വ്‌ വാ നദദ്ധസര ടന്ധദഡ?
It means you are a baboon, and I'm not.
ഗിലിദ്ധാസുയ യ്ലിറി്വാഡിസു, ധിത്ഥ ടര.
I think you're a little confused.
മുര ടടാ യ്ിറിംലശഷ്ബ.
Wrong! I'm not the one who's confused.
ലിവ്‌ ഒധിത്ഥ ടമ ലിഭ്ബ.
-You don't even know who you are. -And I suppose you know.
ഡിവി ടില്വാട 101 ഖല ഡമി ല്ാധിട ഭി ടില്വാ ടര.
Sure do. You're Mufasa's boy.
ഴിനനമന്റാലാബി. ഡല ലല്റ്ഥ്ദട.
-Bye. -Hey, wait!
8൮൭. ല്‍, ധന9്ധ!
You knew my father?
൧ഡിലാനണ്മ്വിരനമ! ഖര ടര?
Correction, I know your father.
ഥലമ്പാബ്ധിന, 1:11 1111-11:
I hate to tell you this,
ഴീടല്‌ ഘന നലമ്പാലി്ച്ധ,
but he died a long time ago.
11 :111:111:11111-1-1:1
Nope. Wrong again!
15 ട്വ!
He's alive, and I'll show him to you.
ഉട നടടി ബ്ലോ, ഠി ടര രഥ ്്വ്ധിറിമ്വാടഠ്ദ യം.
You follow old Rafiki. He knows the way. Come on!
॥ശില്വാല്ംലികി. 8-1 -11111:11:111:111:1
Don't dawdle. Hurry up!
പ്ലിനി നോദ. ല്രോദി
-Hey, whoa, wait, wait. -Come on. Come on!
ല്‍, ധന്ധ, ഡനാഠധ. ഗി. [ീലി!
Would you slow down?
8ഠ1ല൩ യ്ലിലാലിടമ് ടിന
Stop!
ലല്‌!
Look down there.
ല്ലി യല ടന.
That's not my father. That's just my reflection.
ധാധിത്ഥ ഖര ടര. ൮ ഡാന ടര.
No.
ധി.
Look harder.
“1ല്ഠൃ്വാണ്ധ്ാബി.
You see?
പന്വാമ്വല്റ
He lives in you.
ഉട വബിഠ്ധ്വാ ഠ്ല്ടണ ഠി മലി
Simba.
ന്നാ.
Father?
ഷുഖ്്ന
Simba, you have forgotten me.
ന്നാ, മഴമറ നലഥ്വാല്ത് ഷുത്വ.
No. How could I?
1150 ലിറ ടര ഥാലറ്റ്യ?
You have forgotten who you are, and so have forgotten me.
൧ഡലിറിട്വിധ്യാട ടിയാ ഠി യം, 190 യറി നല്ധ്വാലിത്ഥ ഷ൭൨.
Look inside yourself, Simba.
ലിഘി ട്ട 010 മഗ്ല്ം ടിമ്പാദ.
You are more than what you have become.
൧ഡഘിലുദ്ധ്സില്ലിവാലിറ്ട്റോട്മ ട്രാ ൮൭0൧ മഴലിറ്ല്വദഠി ടത.
You must take your place in the circle of life.
൧ഡലി൦ണടട ്॥ ന്മ യ ിട്ണലാധടന ന ിഭ്വ്ോന.
How can I go back? I'm not who I used to be.
റല ടര നലലാധ്ം? മര ലിലി! ട്ട ടലാടല്‍ ദ്ധ.
Remember who you are.
നില ടില്വാദ ഠി മലം
You are my son and the one true king.
൧ഡഘിറന്മി തി ൦ ടദ്ധ-ടഡസ ജ്യ ടലാലന്മല.
No! Please, don't leave me!
പ്ാബ്‌ 7൦൦൮, 000 നഘാടിത്ഥ ടത!
Remember.
നില.
-Father! -Remember!
1! 1 1:1:1:11
Don't leave me.
പാ 0ഘാടിത്ഥ ടര.
Remember.
നില.
What was that?
്വാ ദ്ധ?
The weather.
(ദഠ്ടറ ഡെ.
-Very peculiar, don't you think? -Yeah.
൧൩൭ 0൦൨, 9.
Looks like the winds are changing.
പന്വാമിസുയ 0 ഹാന 9൭0 സ്ധിാബാമ.
Change is good.
ലെഡാമനധ ടടട്ധദ്ധവതന 0ഠ്വട.
Yeah, but it's not easy.
വമ, ല്ല 9 വാധിത്ല ടട സ്വഠ്ട.
I know what I have to do, but going back means I'll have to face my past.
മര 1ദിഡ ലാ ദ്ധ റാഡ്‌, ലവി ലന്നമിന്മ ടര ഹല്ഖ ൫൯3ഠ്ല്ല1 നട ല്ല.
I've been running from it for so long.
1. 1:111-1:111:111 ട്ര നലല്ലിത്ഥ ഠി ഠ്ട്വാ്ദസമ.
Jeez! What was that for?
൧ഠ്ധിവ (നന്ല്വാമ മഴമിവാധമഥാലറ്റ്യ?
It doesn't matter. It's in the past.
൮ ൮00൦൩0. 19 ലിദ്വവാടഠ്ട നടില്ല.
Yeah, but it still hurts.
൭, ഭടലിന്൭ നടടിസലയട.
Yes, the past can hurt.
൭, നടടട ല്ല ന്ധാന നബ്ുഷ്ഖസ്ത്ഥ.
But the way I see it you can either run from it
ലവ മ! ടര ഡേല്‍ ബ്ബ
or learn from it.
ദ്ധ വിവാ ഠ്്വാട്ദസമ.
You see? So what are you going to do?
ല്ലം ൮9ഠി ഖ്വാ നാനാ യല
First, I'm gonna take your stick.
മീധി-ന്ധിമ, ടര നമ്പി യ യല
No, no, no, no! Not the stick!
പ്രാ പം ്ാ॥ എത
-Hey! Where are you going? -I'm going back!
ലി! ള്‍ഡമിന്ല്ലഭ നന? ദ്യ ന്ധി!
Good! Go on! Get out of here!
ദമറ്റ്ട! ലയി ലയ! ലോ ടബ്‌!
Grubs! Grubs!
[1:11]:
Hey. Hey, wake up.
ല്‍. ല്‍, ധാനാഥന.
It's okay! Whoa, whoa! It's okay! It's me!
1ില്വാപ! പസി, ൩! 1ലില്വാഃ! മദര്‌!
Don't ever do that again.
10 നാബാധണ്ലാായ ടയ.
Carnivores!
ലലിധാനമ്സഥ്‌
-Have you guys seen Simba? -l thought he was with you.
ഡമിവലാല്ധദ ദ ന്വാല്സാമ? (൨0 ഠിദ ിവാലടണനട യ്ലി
He was, but now ! can't find him. Where is he?
ഴിനമന്റാാബി, ട്വ ടലി ട്ര 1ിധ്ധന്വാദ ഠി. ൧1൭ 01 നന്മ?
You won't find him here!
൧ഡഘിറവറത്ധസ്വാട ഠി ഠി ടലി!
The king has returned.
മല്യ ടവഠിമവാലബാത്‌ ധി.
I can't believe it. He's gone back!
1 ട്ര. ൧൭ ഠ്ദനാധില്യ!
Gone back? What do you mean?
ലവി? ക്വ നലിത്ധാ ഖല
Hey, what's goin’ on here?
റല, ല്വാട ടഠഠ് ലലില്വ ബി?
-Who's the monkey? -Simba went back to challenge Scar.
മല്യ നു? -ടമ്പാട ൭൨ 0ലഠ] നനാല്ധാല ട്വ.
-Who? -Scar.
-ടല്യാമ? ദ്വേ.
-Who's got a scar? -No, it's his uncle.
-ടില്യാനാനണാഥഡ്ഡ? ലിയ, ലിം ലിന്ുര.
-The monkey's his uncle? -No!
ഗസാല ലിസ്‌? ലിയ
Simba's gone back to challenge his uncle to take his place as king.
ന്നാ 910! നലോ വാലിനു ധന്ധിഗണൃന്സാ॥ (ന്മ ടലാദാദ! ഒ.
Simba, wait up!
ന്ധം, ഡനാധ്‌
-It's awful, isn't it? -I didn't want to believe you.
-ല്ധിപത്ന? ടമ ലാലേ മി ടലോല്ധന ല്‍.
What made you come back?
യാന ൭൨ നന്ഡിത്ഥിന ബ്ന
I finally got some sense knocked into me,
ചന്ന ടടട്ധദ്ധ ലിവ ല്പാല്ല നലമ്പാധിര നട്ട ട്ര,
and I've got the bump to prove it.
നില ട്വ ലാന ശ്വാല്ട ട്ര ഠിധമ്സ൭.
Besides, this is my kingdom.
[മറ 0൨൩, ബി ഭ്ലഘ്യമന ടര.
If l don't fight for it, who will?
ദിദ്ധ ടര പ നലന്പവലന്മ്മിര്സമ, ട്രാ?
-I will. -It's gonna be dangerous.
മൃ മിയ ിപ്വിര്സുമ. 19 ൧3൭1 നലമ്പാടമരിത്ല.
Danger? I laugh in the face of danger.
മല? മപ രയാ ദ്വാലാ॥ിാലടടന്ധിര ലാല്‌.
Il see nothing funny about this.
മയ 1മനാന്വാമിറല്വാ ന്ധ സ്നോ ട്ഡട ബ്‌.
Timon! Pumbaa! What are you doing here?
1നംബ്‌ ല്ധസ്ാദ! ൧്വാട ഴ്ലിവാധട് ഠി ടബ്‌?
At your service, my liege.
ട൭ഠഠിഒലാലിസ്പ്ഠന, ബിവ.
We're gonna fight your uncle for this?
ധ൭ ലിഖ നടിയ ാമഥിറ മയം ടന ഘന ന്മല്‌?
Yes, Timon. This is my home.
൫൭, നന൦0൩. ബില ഡ്ന്ട്വ്വ.
Talk about your fixer-upper!
ഴി ബുയ്വുത്നാ ാഠ്ധ റ്ലാാിവ
Well, Simba, if it's important to you, we're with you to the end.
ന്നാ, യിദ്ധ 1 0൯ 0൮! ഘം, യി മിരിയ ടന്വാല്‍ ഹൃസ്വ.
Hyenas. I hate hyenas.
ഉലാധിം ടര ാലലിത്ഥ ഠ്ധാധിം
So what's your plan for getting past those guys?
൧്വാ നാനാ യ ന്ധി നലില്രാടട। നല്‌?
-Live bait. -Good idea. Hey!
“്്വാന ബിഠ്ധ്വാ. ഠി ന്ാാടാധട. ലി!
Come on, Timon. You guys have to create a diversion.
101൦1൭1൨, നനണ൦൩. ൧ഴലി൦ല്ധം ഗലറ്ധ ലവിഖ്വാന്മി നലല്‍൭.
What do you want me to do, dress in drag and do the hula?
൧്യാട ട്ര വാധ്വ, നായി നേന ൦0൦ ഠ്‌ നന്മ ധി?
Luau!
ധദ്ധ!
If you're hungry for a hunk of fat and juicy meat
287ഒ ഗറഥക്ഥ റ്9ഗ്ഗറ ലന്ഥാഥ്ലുക്ഥറ ല്ല
Eat my buddy Pumbaa here because he is a treat
ഗഒഷ്ഥ൦ ഥാ ൭൭൧൨ ഷ്ഥ്റു ടഗറ്ുററഗ ഒ
Come on down and dine on this tasty swine
എഴഒസഗ ാലടസഖ- 7! 7൭൦൧൮൭൦൧ ല്ല
All you have to do is get in line
൧ഗറ്ദ ലല ഥാലടഥ ട്വ
-Are you achin' -Yep, yep, yep.
ള്‍ഗഠ്ദ 4ലന്നറ്ററ നുര.
-For some bacon?
പീറ്ഖക്ഥ ഥല്ഥ?
-He's a big pig -Yep, yep.
-29 ൧൭൧ റലനഥ മുത.
You could be a big pig, too!
൧ഗറ്ദ ൧൧൧ 2ഠ0൭൨൭൨ റലനഥ്ല്ഥ്ഒ!
Nala, you find my mother and rally the lionesses.
പില, മേധ ടര ഠി വന്ധാധിത്ന ടന്ധട ടിനാലാബ്ന്മ.
I'll look for Scar.
മയ മിത ൧0ലഠ] നന്‌ ട്വ.
Sarabi!
ലാ!
Yes, Scar?
൭, ടല?
Where is your hunting party? They're not doing their job.
ഗി ാടടധി് നലമ്പാധസ ഖല ഴിലഘ്ര 0 നലബുല്മബ്ത്ഥ ധട നലല്‍൭.
Scar, there is no food. The herds have moved on.
ലേ, നല്യ്ഥഥ 6൩12. ലന്ധട യധാനഘ്ഗ ടാ.
No, you're just not looking hard enough.
11-10-11 1111-11. ലോല.
It's over. There is nothing left.
1 ഠദ്വാമിസ്‌7. 11909 ല്വാ3ഠ1 ൮൭൫൩൧ 1094.
We have only one choice. We must leave Pride Rock.
1 സ ട്വ. ൭ നടട! നവബബ്യാദിത്ന ദ്ധ ഥേ.
-We're not going anywhere. -You have sentenced us to death.
(19 19100 ലായ ഭ നന്ന. ധസഡിവന്ന നാടാ! ന്൯ ടസ്ധട.
-Then so be it. -You can't do that.
ഗമി 01ഖില്വാല്റ്ധ. ഡമിവ്മ്വാഠില്‍ല്വാധദ്ലാലവ്വ.
lam the king. l can do whatever I want.
ടമൃയ്്ല്്വ. മൃത ാംില്വാധമ ടിയ ഒ.
If you were half the king Mufasa was...
മിദ്ധ്ല മ്മി ഡിദ്ധ ടലോഡ്ിഭലാക്ല്്ധ്ദട...
I'm ten times the king Mufasa was!
മയ ടല്ധിധ്വിവയി ുദ്ഃ ലാലാ ഠ്വ 'ഴ്ധ്ടട!
Mufasa? No, you're dead.
ഴീധ്ഒടമ? 1991 മഴ്ലിറില നടി.
Mufasa?
ഗ്ധ്ടട?
No. It's me.
ദധി. ബി ടര.
Simba! You're alive? How can that be?
ന്നാ! ൧ഡല൦നടി ബോ? ഗ്ധ്ിന്൩്ര്വാല്ധ?
It doesn't matter. I'm home.
൮ ൮00൦൩0. ദര ഠ്ട്നാധിടന.
Simba?
ടന്ധാമ?
Simba! I'm a little surprised to see you
ന്ധ! 7 ടര ാധിദ ടര മി ന൦॥൫൯ യെ
alive.
നടി ബല്യ.
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't rip you apart.
ദല ട്ര ടവ ടലാലാ ഭനല്വാട ടയ 1മവാ്ഡിഘുല്ത്ന യല
Simba, you must understand.
ന്നാ, 1ഠഘല്വ്ല്മനണ.
The pressures of ruling a kingdom...
ല്രനബുത്നാ ഖര ്ല് ടലനമടദ നനല്‌ന്മ...
Are no longer yours. Step down, Scar.
1ദിലാല്ധ മ! 01ഘാഥനാ ൦1൦൩ യല വധി പന ലം ല്ലേ.
Well, I would, naturally.
൮൭, ലാബി, (ന്ധ ടല.
However, there is one little problem.
ലവ, മഠ ട॥7 നടടലിട ഠി ടി.
You see them?
പന്വാമ്‌ഗനലഘത?
They think I'm king.
ഴിലല്ര ഘാ ടദരതില ദ്വ.
Well, we don't. Simba's the rightful king.
ദ്വി മനമ. നസാ ഠി ഭവം നരാ ടല.
The choice is yours, Scar.
്യാധ്ധട് ഠ ൭൮൩ യല ട്വ.
Either step down or fight.
ധി ലിന്ന്മ മ്ദ്ധിന്മ ലാലാലാ.
Must this all end in violence?
ഴി൦5॥൭൨ ടാലി ാലമിമ്പ ോദബിഭാമന്മട്‌?
I'd hate to be responsible for the death of a family member.
മയ 1ടണല്ഡാന്ഘാഥഘദലാ ട്ട ഭന്0 മല0 ഭ്്ധ ടര.
-Wouldn't you agree, Simba? -That's not gonna work, Scar.
ല്ലി 15 മമ്പാമ? 1ലഒ൨ ഴ്ലിറലിറയ്ാലന്ടടി, ട്വ.
I've put it behind me.
മയ ൭൨ നലഥ്ാല്യ്സമ.
But what about your faithful subjects?
ലവ ലാമ ധി യദ 099 ഹായ ടഖം ദല
Have they put it behind them?
വഠ്ട്വ്യി നല്‍ നലഥ്വാല്ഖ്സര്‌?
Simba, what is he talking about?
൭ന്സാമ, ല്വാുയനാ ഠി ലഭ്യത?
So you haven't told them your little secret.
പഠി യ്ലിവാല്ധണന 9 നല്ല്ത്ഥ ടിം യ്ലി്ലര്വാ്ദ നലല.
Well, Simba, now's your chance to tell them.
ലിറ, മ്പ, ബിദ്വാല്ധമ ധന്ധിഗനലന്പാലന്ല്ഡ നലല്‍൭.
Tell them who is responsible for Mufasa's death.
ലിഭ്വി ടില്വാാാന്ഘാഥാ യല മട നമി ലഴിധ്ടട.
lam.
മത.
It's not true.
൮ ധാന.
Tell me it's not true.
മലി ഖ്ഗധാന്ല.
-It's true. -You see? He admits it!
പ്ഗീനനമറ്റ നല. ലന ഥം നഘാദ്ധയ്‌
-Murderer! -No! It was an accident.
ലമ്പാധന്ധ്വ്‌ ഠി ദ ടവ ഭണടിദ0ല൩.
If it weren't for you, Mufasa would be alive. It's your fault he's dead!
ദിദ്ധ മലമ മമിപ്ഠ്ധ്ടടം ലാട നടി ബാ. ടന്ധേബഭ ടല മിറ
-Do you deny it? -No.
ഗമിനന്മലിര്സുത?
-Then you're guilty. -No, I'm not a murderer!
ഠി ധയ്ണനമ്ാട്ടെലട. 11 ടമുയാധിയ്ന ടം മ്പബാധസ്ധ്വ്‌
Simba, you're in trouble again,
ന്നാ, മഴമറ നടടമില്നില!,
but this time daddy isn't here to save you,
ഖനന രബ ഷുഖ്വലിര്‍്ലാട ടലി ണമിത്ഥ മലം,
and now everyone knows why!
ഠി ടല ടലന്ധദ ൦ ല്ഡഭന൬ല്വാ൪!
Simba!
ന്നാ!
Now, this looks familiar.
ടാ നേന ലാലനമ ബോം
Where have I seen this before? Let me think.
൧ നന്‌? ല്ല ടമ 07.
Yes. l remember.
൭. 8ംബ ടര നാല.
This is just the way your father looked before he died.
൭ ടണട ടലാ൯ ്വാഠ ഖര യ ടലാല്ധന ഠി ന്ധന്ധന.
And here's my little secret.
ദല ടര ലേ്ലിത്ഥ ്ച്ടിട ട്ര ധി.
I killed Mufasa.
മുത ്ന്ാാധസ്ധ്വ്റ്യ്ടം.
No! Murderer!
1 ലാല്പ്ധസ്ധ്ല്‍്‌
-No, Simba, please. -Tell them the truth.
പ്ല, ട്സാടം, 101൦1൭1൨. -ഒലന്ല്ഡ നലലയാലിത്ഥ ടലാലല.
Truth? But truth is in the eye of the behold...
ലലിത്ഥ ടലാന്മല? ലവ ധാ ന്ധന ഭ്വാദഠ്ട ല്ലാ...
All right.
ഒലി.
I did it.
1111111111 ല്‌
So they can hear you.
ന്വാമി നലല്‍ര 001൦ നാട്യ.
I killed Mufasa!
മയ ന്ാധസ്പ്പ്റ്യ്ടം!
Excuse me. Pardon me. Comin’ through. Hot stuff.
ഗി. ന്ധ. ദല ।ച്ധന. ലദ്ന്ട ല്‍.
-Let me out! Let me out! -Let me in! Let me in!
-1ല്ാമടിത് ടര! 1 ലാദടിത്ഥ ട്ര! ജല ട്ര നടി
Please, don't eat me.
10 നലിത്ഥ ടര.
Drop 'em!
പാ ഘാ നലട൪!
-Hey, who's the pig? -Are you talkin’ to me?
ല്‍, ടില്യാലാലാ। വധ? ഡമിവലാലഥലിയ്വാ യോന ടര്‌?
-He called him a pig. -To me?
൧1 നനാ. ലന ടര്‌?
-Shouldn't have done that.
ഗല ഖാദ്ധ്ലാധണ്ലാാസ.
-Now they're in for it. -They call me Mr. Pig!
111:-1:11 1-1 മദര ലാ 2൩. ഒച്1!
Take that, you stupid...
൧്ബാ॥ ലി, 009൦00...
Take that and that!
്വ॥ ബി ദയ
Run, you yellow-belly!
ലല, ണടഥ്‌!
-Murderer. -Simba. Simba, please.
ലമ്പാധന്ധിറ. -ടമ്പാട. സ്വാ, 01൦19.
-Please, have mercy. I beg you. -You don't deserve to live.
-ഒലിത്ഥാലല്‍ദട ൭510൨. ദയര നലയുവ. ഗമിവല്ലപരിറി്ലിത്ഥ ബ്ലോ.
But Simba, l am family.
ല്വാ। മ്പാഃ, ൯൭ ലടദ്ധഠ്മമ.
It's the hyenas who are the real enemy.
ഉലാധിറ്ല സ്വപ്ന ടലാന്മ്വ.
It was their fault. It was their idea.
ല്ധസുട ടട1മ൨ നല. 11-11-11
Why should I believe you?
(ദറ്വാ ടര വാ്ധ്ലാലമുതയിത്ഥ യല
Everything you ever told me was a lie.
ലട യ്യ ടല ല്‍ 5൩ വാല്പാ0൦൭൭൩.
What are you going to do?
യാന വത്ഥ ഖ്ലിവാധ
You wouldn't kill your own uncle.
ദിന യലി൦നലി്ഥധന്ഥ 031 ലി യല ടി.
No, Scar.
11, ടല്ലേ.
I'm not like you.
ഭമുതാധിത്ല ടല ദമം
Simba, thank you. You are truly noble.
സ്വാ, ലിന 51൨. ൧ഡിണനണനമനാ സ്ധിദ.
I'll make it up to you, I promise. And how can I prove myself to you?
മയ്യ! ല്ല നലമ്പാദ്ടട ാധഠി ലി 8൦1 ടഖരാധിനിത്ന ഭട ടര്‌?
Tell me. l mean, anything.
ലിഭ്വിം൨. ഴി ല്വാ ടല്്മ.
Run.
ലി.
Run away, Scar,
10 ഠി ട്[ബി, ടേ,
and never return.
ബനാന അ്വദ॥.
Yes.
വ.
Of course.
“ലന്ധ ടല.
As you wish,
ഴി ന്മ,
your Majesty!
ന്ധബിയ്‌
My friends!
ലല്ല ടല്ലാട്‌ ട്ര!
Friends? I thought he said we were the enemy.
ലാറ 8ധിയ്ബ്യ ഠി ഠി തട ന൭ സ്വര.
Yeah. That's what I heard.
൭. മര ഥന റോ ലാലൃധ്ധ.
Ed?
ഠി
No. Let me explain. No, you don't understand!
ദധി. ച ടരയലദടിത്ന. 8ധിദ്വ, മഗ്ല്റല്റ്ല്ഘന!
No, I didn't mean... No! No!
ദധി, ടര 0 നലിത്ധാ।ത്ഥ... പ്രാ പംാദ്ബ്‌
It is time.
ഉലാ നടു.
Remember.
ഗുല.
Till we find our place
൧0൭7 :ഗ്൭ നലലനഥ്‌ “ലന്വാദ! ഗ്ഒ
On the path unwinding
൧൭൧ഥ )൭൧ഥറ ൧൦൧ 777൨
In the circle
൧ ൭ഒന 0ാഥ5ഗറ്റണറ
The circle of life
൧5൧൭ :കറ്ഥാറെ
Circle of
൧൧ഥറ്ഥ
Life
ലാറ്ഥാറെ